让我告诉你"宛若处女"说的是什么
Let me tell you what "Like A Virgin" is about.
是说一个姑娘找到一个大老二的男人
It's all about a girl who digs a guy with a big dick.
整首歌就是暗指大老二
The entire song is a metaphor for big dicks.
不 不是的
No it ain't.
是说一个非常敏感的妞
It's about a girl who's very vulnerable.
她有过几次性经验
She's been fucked over a few times
然后遇上一个敏感的男人
and she meets a guy who's sensitive.
歇歇吧 这些废话拿去唬弄游客好了
Whoa. Timeout. Tell that bullshit to the tourists.
塔比? 谁是他妈的塔比?
Toby? Who the fuck is Toby?
"宛若处女"不是说什么
"Like A Virgin" is not about some
一个敏感的姑娘遇见一个好小伙子
sensitive girl who meets a nice fella.
那是"绝对忧郁"说的故事
That's what "True Blue" is about. No argument about that.
- 哪首歌是"绝对忧郁"? - 是麦当娜的一首热门上榜歌曲
- Which one is "True Blue"? - It was a big- ass hit for Madonna.
我从不关心什么狗屁排行榜
I don't even follow that top- of- the- pops shit
但我听过这首歌
and I've heard of "True Blue."
我不会说我没听过
I didn't say I ain't heard of it.
我只想知道它讲了什么
All I asked is how's it go?
很抱歉我不是世上最爱麦当娜的歌迷
Excuse me for not being the world's biggest Madonna fan.
没有她我也能活下去
Personally I can do without her.
我曾经喜欢她早期的歌 "边缘"...
I used to like her early stuff "Borderline"...
但从她唱了那首"爸爸 不要说教"之后
but once she got off with that "Papa Don't Preach" phase
我就不喜欢了
I tuned out.
嘿 你们这些家伙打断了我的思路
Hey you guys are making me lose my train of thought here.
我刚才讲到哪了?
I was sayin' something. What was it?
哦 那个中国小姑娘塔比
Oh Toby's that little Chinese girl.
- 她姓什么来着? - 那是什么?
- What was her last name? - What's that?
是我在一件旧外套里
It's an old address book I found in a coat
找到的一本旧地址簿
I haven't worn in a coon's age.
- 那名字是什么? - 我他妈的在讲什么来着?
- What was that name? - What the fuck was I talkin' about?
你说"绝对忧郁"讲一个...
You said "True Blue" was about a guy...
一个敏感的妞遇上一个棒小伙...
a sensitive girl who meets a nice guy...
但"宛若处女"是个暗指大老二的故事
but "Like A Virgin" was a metaphor for big dicks.
让我告诉你"宛若处女"是讲什么
Let me tell you what "Like A Virgin" is about.
它讲的是一个职业性交机器的经历
It's all about this cooze who's a regular fuck machine.
我是指早上 白天 晚上 下午...
I'm talkin' morning day night afternoon...
老二 老二...
dick dick dick dick dick dick dick dick dick!
- 有多少个"老二"? - 很多
- How many "dicks" is that? - A lot.
然后有一天 她遇见约翰·荷莫斯那个混蛋
Then one day she meets this John Holmes motherfucker.
一个大惊喜
It's like "Whoa baby."
那混蛋就象"大逃亡"里的主角
He's like Charles Bronson in "The Great Escape."
他插进"隧道" 现在她见识了真正的老二
He's diggin' tunnels. Now she's gettin' serious dick action.
她体会到久违的感觉 痛 痛
She's feelin' somethin' she ain't felt since forever: pain pain.
朱 塔比·朱?
Chew? Toby Chew?
她被弄伤了
It hurts. It hurts her.
她不应该痛 她的私处本该是充满快感的
It shouldn't hurt her. Her pussy should be Bubble- Yum by now.
但那家伙干她时 就是痛
But when this cat fucks her it hurts.
痛得就象是第一次一样
It hurts just like it did the first time.
疼痛让这个性交机器记起了...
You see the pain is reminding a fuck machine...
还是处女时的那次感觉
what it was once like to be a virgin.
因此 叫"宛若处女"
Hence "Like A Virgin."
王
Wang.
- 把那该死的东西给我 - 你以为你是谁?
- Give me that fuckin' thing. - What in hell do you think you're doin'?
我讨厌听你说这个 乔 我会在走的时候还给你
I'm sick of hearin' it Joe. I'll give it back to you when we leave.
什么意思 走的时候? 马上还给我
What do you mean when we leave? Give me it back now!
过去十五分钟你都在念叨这些名字
For the past 15 minutes now you've been droning on about names.
塔比 塔比?
"Toby. Toby?
塔比? 塔比·王
Toby? Toby Wong.
塔比·王? 塔比·王
Toby Wong? Toby Wong.
塔比·张 去他妈的查理·陈
Toby Chung fuckin' Charlie Chan."
我左耳朵听到的是麦当娜的大老二
I've got Madonna's big dick comin' out of my left ear...
而塔比那个日本...不管是什么人 却出现在我的右耳朵
and Toby the Jap...I don't know what...comin' out of my right.
把本子给我
Give me that book.
你会把它放在一边吗?
Are you gonna put it away?
我想他妈的干什么就干什么
I'm gonna do whatever the fuck I want with it.
那我恐怕只好继续保管它
Well then I'm afraid I'm gonna have to keep it.
嘿 乔 要我开枪崩了这家伙吗?
Hey Joe want me to shoot this guy?
妈的
Shit.
你做梦对我开过枪 醒来后最好向我道歉
You shoot me in a dream you better wake up and apologize.
你们听过
You guys been listenin'
K·比利做的"70年代超级声"吗?
to K- BILLY's "Super Sounds of the '70s" weekend?
听过 节目非常棒
Yeah. That's fuckin' great.
你相信他们在歌里唱的吗?
You believe the songs they're playin'?
知道我那时候听什么?
Know what I heard the other day?
东尼·迪弗朗科和家人唱的
"Heartbeat It's a Lovebeat"
"心跳 是爱的悸动"
by little Tony DeFranco and the DeFranco family.
我到十五年级之后就再没听过
I haven't heard that song since I was in the fifth fuckin' grade.
我到这时
When I was comin'down here
"乔治亚黑夜"刚问世
"The Night the Lights Went Out in Georgia" came on.
这首歌流行起来后我就没听过了
I ain't heard that song since it was big.
但它流行的时候
But when it was big
我肯定听过无数次
I must've heard it a million- trillion fuckin' times.
那是我第一次了解到...
But this is the first time I ever realized...
那姑娘唱的那首歌 就是枪杀安迪的那首
that the girl singin' the song is the one who shot Andy.
你不知道 是维奇·罗伦斯枪杀了安迪?
You didn't know that Vickie Lawrence was the one who shot Andy?
我以为是个不忠的妻子枪杀了安迪
I thought the cheatin' wife shot Andy.
他们说那是那首歌的结尾
They say that at the end of the song.
我知道 混蛋 我听说是这样 所以才这么说
I know motherfucker.I just heard it.That's what I'm talkin' about.
我以前肯定是漏听了那部分
I must've zoned out during that part before.
好了 我来付帐
All right I'll take care of the check.
你们自己付小费
You guys can get the tip.
每人一块钱
Should be about a buck apiece.
你 我回来时把本子还给我
And you when I come back I want my book.
对不起 现在它是我的
Sorry. It's my book now.
嘿 我改主意了 毙了这混蛋好吗?
Hey I changed my mind. Shoot this piece of shit will ya?
好了 每人掏一块钱给那位年轻女士
All right everybody cough up some green for the little lady.
快 就一块钱
Come on throw in a buck.
我不付小费
I don't tip.
- 你不付小费? - 我不赞成这个
- You don't tip? - I don't believe in it.
你不赞成付小费?
You don't believe in tipping?
你知道这些姑娘能挣多少吗? 少得可怜
Do you know what these chicks make? They make shit.
她挣不到足够的钱就会辞职不干
If she don't make enough money she can quit.
我从不知道 一个该死的犹太人会这么说
I don't even know a fuckin' Jew who'd have the balls to say that.
别怪我这么直接 你从不付小费吗?
Let me get this straight. You don't ever tip huh?
我不给小费是因为社会说我必须给
I don't tip because society says I have to.
如果她们真的尽力工作了 我会给她们额外的报酬
If they really put forth the effort I'll give 'em somethin' extra.
而现在是主动给她们小费
But this tipping automatically it's for the birds.
我觉得她们只是尽了自己的本份
As far as I'm concerned they're just doin' their job.
- 这姑娘不错 - 她没问题
- This girl was nice. - She was okay.
- 但也没什么特别 - 怎样算特别?
- She wasn't anything special. - What's special?
带你回家然后舔你的老二?
Take you in the back and suck your dick?
那我愿意为此多给12%
I'd go over 12% for that.
我叫了咖啡对吗? 她只给我添了三次
I ordered coffee all right? She's only filled my cup three times.
我想要六次
I want it filled six times.
六次? 如果她太忙呢?
Six times? Well what if she's too fuckin' busy?
侍应生的字典里
The words"too fuckin' busy"
不该有"太忙"这个词
shouldn't be in a waitress's vocabulary.
抱歉 粉先生 你无非就是想要...
Excuse me Mr. Pink but the last fuckin' thing you need's...
另一杯咖啡
another cup of coffee.
这些侍应不会饿死 她们有最低收入保障
These ladies aren't starvin' to death. They make minimum wage.
我也拿过低保 可那时...
I used to work minimum wage and when I did...
我并没幸运到有人认为
I wasn't lucky enough to have a job
值得付小费
that society deemed tip- worthy.
你不在乎她们是靠你的小费维生?
You don't care they're countin' on your tips to live?
知道这是什么意思吗?
You know what this is?
这是世上最小的小提琴 只为侍应生演奏
The world's smallest violin playin' just for the waitresses.
你一点也不知道你在说的是什么
You don't have any idea what you're talkin' about.
这些人忙得不可开交 这是份辛苦的工作
These people bust their ass. This is a hard job.
在麦当劳工作也一样 但你不会觉得该付她们小费
So's working at McDonald's but you don't feel the need to tip them.
她们为你服务 但是社会说..
They're servin' you food but society says...
"别给那些人小费 但要给这些人" 全是胡说
"Don't tip these guys over here but tip these guys." That's bullshit.
侍应生是这个国家...
Waitressing is the number- one occupation...
没受过大学教育的女性的首选职业
for female non- college graduates in this country.
这份工作关键在于 任何女人都能胜任并赖以谋生
It's the one job basically any woman can get and make a living on.
原因就在于她们的小费
The reason is because of their tips.
去他妈的
Fuck all that.
很遗憾政府要对她们的小费征税
I'm very sorry the government taxes their tips.
真是糟透了 但那不是我的错
That's fucked up. That ain't my fault.
这说明侍应生是众多...
It would appear that waitresses are one of the many groups...
不时受到政府欺压的群体之一
the government fucks in the ass on a regular basis.
给我一份说政府不该这样干的报纸
Show me a paper that says the government shouldn't do
我会签名
that I'll sign it.
我会表示支持 但我不会做发起人
I'll vote for it. But what I won't do is play ball.
至于未受过大学教育
This non- college bullshit
我称之为:不学好样
I got two words for that: Learn to fuckin' type.
如果你指望我为此掏钱
If you're expectin' me to help out with the rent
那你会大失所望
you're in for a big surprise.
有道理 把我的钱还我
He's convinced me. Give me my dollar back.
嘿 别碰那些钱
Hey. Leave the dollars there.
好了 各位 我们走吧
All right ramblers let's get ramblin'.
等等 谁没掏钱?
Wait a minute. Who didn't throw in?
- 粉先生 - 粉先生?
- Mr. Pink. - Mr. Pink?
- 为什么? - 他不付小费
- Why not? - He don't tip.
他不付小费?
He don't tip?
- 你不付小费? - 他不赞成
- You don't tip? - He don't believe in it.
闭嘴 什么意思 你不赞成这样做?
Shut up. What do you mean you don't believe in it?
快掏钱 你这下流坯
Cough up a buck you cheap bastard.
我已经请你们吃了他妈的早餐
I paid for your goddamn breakfast.
既然你请了早餐 我掏钱好了
Since you bought breakfast I'll put in.
但平时我可不干
But normally I would never do this.
不管你平时怎么做
Never mind what you normally would do.
只管象其他人一样 掏出你那该死的一块钱 谢谢
Just cough in your goddamn buck like everybody else. Thank you.
这是帕特里奇家族
That was the Partridge Family's
上演的"谁想逃帐? "
"Doesn't Somebody Want To Be Wanted? "...
接下来是爱迪生·莱特豪斯的..
followed by Edison Lighthouse's...
"爱随我的迷迭香成长"
"Love Grows Where My Rosemary Goes"...
就象K·比利的 "70年代超级声"一样
as K- BILLY's "Super Sounds of the '70s" weekend...
请继续收听
just keeps on truckin'.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die!
坚持住 伙计
Just hold on buddy boy!
我要死了
I'm gonna die!
- 对不起 - 把你的手给我
- I'm sorry! - Give me your hand.
真不敢相信她想杀了我 老兄 有谁能料到?
I can't believe she killed me man! Who'd have fuckin' thought that?
嘿 现在别说那些废话了
Hey just cancel that shit right now!
你受了伤 确实伤得很重 但你不会死
You're hurt. You're hurt real fuckin' bad but you ain't dying!
这些血吓死我了 拉里
All this blood's scarin' the shit out of me Larry!
我要死了 我知道
I'm gonna die! I know it!
抱歉 我不知道你有医学学位
Excuse me I didn't realize you had a degree in medicine.
你是医生?
Are you a doctor?
你是医生吗?
请回答我 你是医生吗?
Answer me please! Are you a doctor?
不 我不是 我不是
No I'm not. I'm not.
那么你承认不知道自己在说什么了
So you admit you don't know what you're talkin' about.
如果你说完了你的业余看法
If you're through givin' me your amateur opinion
躺回去听我说
lie back and listen.
我带你到会合地点
I'm takin' you back to the rendezvous
乔会替你找个医生
Joe's gonna get you a doctor...
医生会给你治伤...
the doctor's gonna fix you up and...
你会没事的
you're gonna be okay.
现在说:"你会没事的"
Now say it! You're gonna be okay!
说啊
Say it!
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay!
把这该死的话说出来 你会没事的
Say the goddamn words! You're gonna be okay!
上帝啊
Oh God!
他妈的说啊
Say the goddamn fuckin' words!
说
Say it!
好的 拉里
Okay Larry.
好好说 好好说
Correct! Correct!
我很好
I'm okay.
看看我们到哪了
Look where we are.
她怀了孩子 老兄 她怀了孩子
She had a baby man. She had a baby!
我们在仓库里
We're in a warehouse.
谁是硬汉? 谁是硬汉?
Who's a tough guy? Who's a tough guy?
- 回答我 谁是硬汉? - 我是硬汉
- Come on who's a tough guy? - I am a tough guy
谁是硬汉? 你是硬汉
Who's a tough guy? You're a tough guy.
你是个他妈的硬汉
You're a fuckin' tough guy.
我们在仓库里 看看我们在哪
We're in a warehouse. Look where we are.
我们到了 我们到了
We made it. We made it.
我们他妈的到了 我们现在他妈的到了
We fuckin' made it. We have fuckin' made it.
我们在仓库里 看看我们在哪
We're in a warehouse. Look where we are.
看看我们在哪
Look where we are.
撑住 撑住
Hold on. Hold on.
- 妈的 - 别再撞你的头
- Shit! - Stop bangin' your head.
你要在地板上撞出一个洞来了
You're gonna bang a fuckin' hole in the floor.
你不想弄坏他妈的地板对吗?
You don't wanna hurt the fuckin' floor do you?
我没法为你做任何事
I can't do anything for you.
但只要乔一到这...
But when Joe gets here...
他随时都会赶来...
which should be any time now...
他会帮助你 会照顾你
he's gonna help you out he's gonna take care of you.
我们得坐下等着乔
We're gonna sit and wait for Joe.
- 我们在等谁? - 乔
- Who are we waitin' for? - Joe.
拉里 我他妈的害怕 老兄
Larry I'm fucking scared man.
你能抱着我吗?
Would you please hold me?
是的 当然
Yeah sure.
你有理由害怕
You go ahead and be scared.
你今天已经够勇敢的了
You've been brave enough for one day.
现在我要你放松 明白吗?
I just want you to relax now okay?
你不会死 你会好起来的
You're not gonna fuckin' die. You're gonna be fine.
乔一到这 就会让你完好如初的
When Joe gets here he'll make you 100% again.
我受伤了是吗? 我伤得很重 拉里
Am I hurt? I'm hurt bad Larry.
情况是不太妙
It's not good no.
嘿 拉里
Hey Larry...
感谢你为我做的努力
bless your heart for what you're tryin' to do.
我刚才在那惊慌失措
I was panicking for a minute back there.
但是我现在清醒过来了
But I got my senses back now.
现在的情况是我腹部中枪
The situation is I'm shot in the belly.
没有医生救治我会死的
Without medical attention I'm gonna die.
- 我不能带你去医院 - 去他妈的监狱 老兄
- I can't take you to a hospital. - Fuck jail man!
你不用带我进去 只要把我送到门口就行
You don't have to take me in. Just drive me up to the front man.
把我扔在人行便道上 我会照顾自己
Just drop me on the sidewalk. I'll take care of myself.
我不会告诉他们任何事 老兄 我什么都不会说
I won't tell 'em anything man. I won't tell 'em anything.
我向他妈的上帝发誓 老兄
I swear to fucking God man.
看着我的眼睛 拉里 看着我的眼睛
Just look in my eyes Larry. Look in my eyes.
我什么都不会告诉他们
I won't tell them anything.
你会很安全 老兄
You'll be safe man.
你不会他妈的死掉 小伙子 对吗?
You're not gonna fuckin' die kid. All right?
听我说 你会好起来的
Listen to me. You're gonna be fine.
和膝盖一样...
Along with the kneecap...
内脏被打中是最痛的部位
the gut is the most painful area a guy can get shot in.
别说笑了
No shit!
但是要过很长时间才会致命
But it takes a long time to die from it.
得好几天
I'm talkin' days.
你会宁可死掉
You're gonna wish you were dead
但是得好几天你才会死
but it takes days to die from your wound.
你有的是时间
Time is on your side.
那是不是个他妈的圈套?
Was that a fucking setup or what?
该死 橙挂彩了?
Shit. Orange got tagged?
腹部中枪
Gut shot.
妈的 褐在哪?
Fuck. Where's Brown?
死了
Dead.
怎么死的?
How did he die?
他妈的你以为呢? 警察击毙了他
How the fuck do you think? The cops shot him.
真是糟糕
This is bad.
是他妈的非常糟 不是吗?
This is so fucking bad. Is it bad?
相对"好"而言吗?
As opposed to good?
老兄 真是糟糕
Man this is fucked up.
真是太糟糕了
This is so fucked up.
有人出卖了我们 老兄
Somebody fucked us up big time man.
- 你真的觉得我们是中了埋伏? - 你一点不怀疑吗?
- You really think we were set up? - Do you even doubt it man?
我们肯定是中了埋伏 我知道
I don't think we got set up I know it.
所有那些警察是从哪来的 嗯?
Where did all those cops come from huh?
前一分钟还不在 下一分钟就来了
One minute they're not there and the next minute they're there.
我根本没听到警报声 警报器响了是吗?
I didn't hear any sirens. The alarm went off okay?
当警报响了之后 你得要四分钟来作出反应
When an alarm goes you got a four- minute response time.
如果不是有辆巡逻车 正好在那条街上的话
Unless a patrol car is cruising that street at that moment...
在他们能作出反应之前你有四分钟
you got four minutes before they can realistically respond.
一分钟内 有十七个警察出现..
In one minute there were 17 blue boys out there...
全都清楚他们在嘛
all knowing exactly what the fuck they were doing
他们早就埋伏在那了
and they were all there!
记得第二批出现的警车吗?
Remember that second wave that showed up in the cars?
那才是听到警报后赶来的
Those were the ones responding to the alarm
但第一批混蛋
but those first motherfuckers...
是早就埋伏在那的
they were there and they were waitin' for us.
你他妈的就没想过这些吗?
Haven't you fuckin' thought about this?
我根本没机会去想
I haven't had a chance to think.
我首先想到的就是他妈的逃跑
First I was just tryin' to get the fuck outta there.
而我们逃脱之后 我一直和他在一起
And after we got away I've just been dealin' with him.
最好快想 因为这很重要
Better start thinkin' about it 'cause that's all I'm thinkin' about.
我甚至不想来这 我想开车逃走 老兄...
I wasn't even gonna come here. I was just gonna drive off man...
因为不管内奸是谁 他都知道这地方
because whoever set us up knows about this place.
这里可能有警察在等着
There could've been cops here waitin'!
也许现在警察正在赶来
There could be cops comin' right now!
我们去另一个房间 嘿 在那边
Let's go in the other room. Hey. In there.
拉里 别离开我
Larry don't leave me.
我就在另一个房间好吗? 我会在那看着你
I'll be right in the other room okay? I'll be right there lookin' at ya.
我会在这看着你 好吗?
I'm right here lookin' at you okay?
我就在那边
I'm right over there.
拉里
Larry...
我他妈的要死了
I'm gonna fucking die.
拉里
Larry.
我他妈的在这干什么? 老兄
What the fuck am I doin' here man?
我觉得这活太有趣了
I felt funny about this job right off.
我一有这种感觉就该放弃
As soon as I felt it I should have said"No thank you"
但我没有
but I never fuckin' listen.
我每次买大麻都会这样
Every time I ever got fucked buying weed the same thing.
我不相信那家伙 但我想相信他
I didn't trust the guy but I wanted to believe him.
如果他没说谎而且真是泰国大麻 那倒也不错
If he's not lying and it really is Thai stick then it's great.
但从来都不是
But it never is
我总说行动时有那种感觉我就离开
and I always said that if I felt that about a job I'd fuckin' walk.
但我没有 我没离开是因为该死的钱
And I didn't. I didn't because of the fuckin' money!
过去的就过去了 你冷静点
What's done is done. I need you cool.
你冷静了吗?
Are you cool?
我很冷静
I'm cool.
往脸上泼点水
Splash some water on your face.
做个深呼吸
Take a breather.
放松下来 抽支烟
Relax. Have a cigarette.
我戒了
I quit.
- 好吧 - 来支也好 你有吗?
- All right. - Why you got one?
好了 我们来想想发生了什么事
Okay let's go through what happened.
我们到了那 一切都很顺利
We're in the place everything's going fine.
然后警铃响了
Then the alarm gets tripped.
我一转身看到那些警察在外面
I turn around and all these cops are outside.
你说的没错 就象变魔术一样 我眨眨眼他们就在那了
You're right. It was like bam I blinked my eyes and they're there.
大家都开始惊慌 然后金先生开了枪
Everybody starts going ape- shit.Then Mr. Blonde starts to shoot all
- 不是这样 - 有什么不对?
- That's not correct. - What's wrong with it?
警铃响了后警察并没出现
Okay. The cops did not show up after the alarm went off.
金先生向所有人开枪之前
The cops didn't show up until after
警察并没出现
Mr. Blonde started shootin' everybody.
- 接着我听到警铃声 看到了警察 - 并没那么快
- Soon as I heard the alarm I saw cops. - It wasn't that soon.
在金先生发疯之前
They didn't let their presence be known
他们并没出现
until after Mr. Blonde became a madman.
我不是说他们不在那 他们早就在
I'm not sayin' they weren't there. I'm sayin' they were there.
但是他们
But they didn't make a move
在金先生开枪之前没有行动
until after Mr. Blonde started shootin' everybody.
所以我才知道是中了埋伏
I mean that's how I know we were set up.
- 白先生 你能看到的 - 别再叫什么鬼"白先生"了
- Mr. White you can see that... - Enough of this "Mr. White" shit.
等等 别告诉我你叫什么鬼名字 我不想知道
Wait! Don't tell me you're fuckin' name! I don't wanna know it!
老天 我可不想告诉你我叫什么
Jesus Christ I ain't gonna tell you mine.
你是对的 那没好处
You're right. This is bad.
- 你是怎么逃脱的? - 我杀出了一条血路
- How did you get out? - I shot my way out.
所有人都在开枪 所以我趁乱逃了出来
Everybody started shootin' so I blasted my way out of there.
躲开 让开路 他妈的让开路
Move it! Get outta the way! Get the fuck outta the way!
他妈的快躲开
Get the fuck outta the way!
让开 把路让开
Move it! Get outta the way!
老天 你他妈的有问题吗 老兄?
Jesus Christ! What the fuck is your problem man?
- 你这该死的混蛋 - 去你妈的
- You fuckin' asshole! - Fuck you!
让开
Move!
天啊
Jesus!
从车里出来 他妈的从车上下来
Get outta the car! Get the fuck outta the car!
闪开 从路上闪开
Move it! Move outta the way!
我打伤了几个警察
I tagged a couple of cops.
你杀了什么人吗?
Did you kill anybody?
- 几个警察 - 没有行人?
- A few cops. - No real people?
只杀了警察
Just cops.
你信任金先生吗?
Could you believe Mr. Blonde?
那是我曾见过的最疯狂的事
That was the most insane fuckin' thing I have ever seen.
乔为什么找个这样的家伙?
Why the fuck would Joe hire a guy like that?
我不想杀人
I don't want to kill anybody.
但如果你想挡我的路...
If I gotta get out that door and you're standin' in my way...
要么我杀了你 要么你就让开
one way or the other you're gettin' outta my way.
这是我看待事情的方式
That's the way I look at it.
是坐十年牢...
The choice between doin' ten years...
还是干掉一个愚蠢的混蛋...
and takin' out some stupid motherfucker...
只能选择其一
ain't no choice at all.
但我并不是疯子
But I ain't no madman either.
乔他妈怎么想的?
What the fuck was Joe thinkin'?
你没法和那种家伙共事
You can't work with a guy like that.
万幸的是
We're awful goddamn lucky
他在那乱射一气时没伤到我们
he didn't tag us when he shot the place up.
他的屁股离我的只有这么远
I came this close to takin' his ass out myself.
我是说 所有人都很惊慌 所有人
I mean everybody panics. Everybody.
形势紧急 那是人的自然反应
Things get tense. It's human nature.
人的惊慌是无法控制的
You panic. I don't care what your name is you can't help it.
妈的 老兄 惊慌是发自内心的 知道吗?
Fuck man you panic on the inside in your head you know?
你给自己几秒钟
You give yourself a couple of seconds
看清楚形势
get ahold of it and deal with it.
你就不会在那
What you don't do is start shootin' up the place
开枪杀人
and start killin' people.
你的举动应该显得专业一点
What you're supposed to do is act like a fuckin' professional.
一个精神病患不会是专业人士
A psychopath ain't a professional.
你无法和一个疯子共事
You can't work with a psychopath.
你不知道那些混蛋下一步会干嘛
You don't know what those sick assholes are gonna do next.
我是说 老天
I mean Jesus Christ
你觉得那个黑人女孩有多大? 二十?
how old do you think that black girl was? Twenty?
- 也许二十一? - 大概吧
- Maybe 21? - If that.
你知道其他人的情况吗?
Did you see what happened to anybody else?
我和橙跳上了车 褐被打死了
Me and Orange jumped in the car Brown floored it.
之后的事我就不知道了
After that I don't know what went down.
大家只能各顾各
It was every man for himself.
至于金先生和蓝先生
As far as Mr. Blonde and Mr. Blue are concerned
我不清楚
I ain't got the foggiest...
我一逃出去就没回头看过
cause once I got out I never looked back.
你怎么想?
What do you think?
我怎么想? 他们不是被抓了就是被杀了
What do I think? The cops either caught 'em or killed 'em.
没机会逃脱吗? 你就逃脱了
No chance they punched through? You found a hole.
对 但这是个他妈的奇迹
Yeah and that was a fuckin' miracle.
就算他们逃脱了 那他们在哪?
But even if they did get away then where the
fuck are they?
你没想过
You don't think
他们可能拿了钻石然后...
it's possible one of 'em got ahold of the diamonds and...
- 不 决不会 - 你怎么这样肯定?
- No no way. - How can you be so sure?
我拿了钻石
I got the diamonds.
好伙计
That's my boy.
- 在哪? - 我藏起来了
- Where? - I stashed 'em.
如果你想和我一起走 我们马上就去拿
If you wanna come with me let's go get 'em right now this second.
因为我觉得留在这 老兄
'Cause I think stayin' here man
我们就该检查一下脑袋了
we should have our fuckin' heads examined.
原计划是在这会面
That was the plan. We meet here.
那其他人在哪?
Then where the fuck is everybody?
只要发现有内奸
I say the plan becomes null
计划就可以取消
and void once we found out we got a rat here.
金先生和蓝先生
We ain't got the slightest idea
下落不明
what happened to Mr. Blonde or Mr. Blue.
可能完了 也可能被抓住了
They could both be dead or maybe they're arrested.
警察也许正在
The cops could have 'em right now
警局盘问他们
at the station sweatin' 'em down.
他们不知道我们叫什么
They don't know our names
但也许会供出这地方
but they could be singin' about this place.
我向上帝发誓 我觉得我是个扫把星
I swear to God I think I'm fuckin' jinxed.
什么?
What?
有次买卖是四个人一起干的
Two jobs back it was a four- man job.
我们发现其中一个是警方的卧底
We discovered one of the team was an undercover cop.
不是吧?
No shit?
感谢上帝我们及时发现了
Thank God we discovered in time.
我们只好放弃整个计划 一走了之
We had to forget the whole thing just walk the fuck away from it.
那这次谁是内奸?
So who's the rat this time?
蓝先生?
Mr. Blue?
褐先生?
Mr. Brown?
乔? 乔策划的整个计划 也许全都是他在捣鬼
Joe? Joe set this whole thing up. Maybe he set it up to set it up.
我不这么想 我和乔认识很久了
I don't buy it. Me and Joe go back a long time.
我可以断然告诉你
I can tell you definitely
乔对这个圈套一无所知
Joe didn't know a thing about this bullshit.
我了解乔 如果我说他肯定
I know Joe and me sayin' he definitely
和这无关就太可笑了
had nothin' to do with it is ridiculous.
我可以断定不是我
I can say I definitely didn't do it
我知道自己做没做
cause I know what I did or didn't do.
但我无法断定其他人有没有做
But I cannot definitely say that about
因为确实不知道
anybody cause I don't definitely know.
在我看来 你就是内奸
For all I know you're the rat.
在我看来 你才是他妈的内奸
For all I know you're the fuckin' rat!
很好 现在你他妈的在用脑子了
All right now you're usin' your fuckin' head.
现在看来 他是内奸
For all we know he's the rat.
这孩子快死了 我亲眼看到他中枪...
That kid in there is dying from a fuckin' bullet I saw him take...
所以你不能说他是内奸
so don't you be calling him a rat!
听着 我是对的 明白吗?
Look I'm right okay?
有人是他妈的内奸
Somebody's a fuckin' rat.
这地牢的厕所在哪? 我要撒尿
Where's the commode in this dungeon? I gotta take a squirt.
沿走廊一直走 左转 上楼梯...
Go down the hall make a left go up the stairs...
然后右转
and make a right.
- 顺便问一下 阿拉巴马怎么样? - 阿拉巴马?
- By the way how's Alabama? - Alabama?
我有一年半没见过她了
I haven't seen Bama in over a year and a half.
但我想你们俩是一组的
But I thought you two were a team.
有段时间是
We were for a little while.
一起干了四次买卖 然后决定拆伙
Did about four jobs together then decided to call it quits.
为什么?
Why?
你做那种男男女女的事太久
You push that woman- man thing too long
一段时间后就会对你有影响
and it gets to you after a while.
她现在在干嘛?
What's she doin' now?
她搭上了弗兰克- 麦加
She hooked up with Frank McGar.
他们一起干了几票
They've done a couple jobs together.
该死的女人 精明的小贼
Hell of a woman. Good little thief.
白先生
- 电报里说了什么 - 五个人的工作
- So explain the telegram. - Five- man job.
一个钻石批发商的场子
Bustin' in and bustin' out of a diamond wholesaler's.
事后你能脱手吗?
Can you move the ice afterwards?
我可没这种熟人
I don't know nobody that can move ice.
没问题 有人正在等这批货
No problem. We got guys waitin' for it.
马赛罗- 斯派维怎么了?
What happened to Marcellus Spivey?
他不是一直处理你的钻石吗?
Didn't he always move your ice?
他要在苏珊维尔蹲二十年大狱
He's doin' 20 years in Susanville.
二十年 上帝 怎么回事?
Twenty years? Holy God. What for?
运气不好
Bad luck.
我猜你会这么说
I guess you can say that again.
行动要多长时间?
What's the exposure like?
最多两分钟 但很棘手
Two minutes tops. But it's a tough two minutes.
白天 交易时间 大群的人
Daylight during business hours dealing with a crowd.
但会有人帮你应付人群
But you'll have the guys to deal with the crowd.
- 有多少店员? - 二十个左右
- How many employees? - I'd say around 20.
保安相当松懈
Security pretty lax.
他们平时的主要业务是打包
They most usually just deal in boxes.
来自钻石财团的未经切割的钻石
You know uncut stones from the diamond syndicate.
但那天他们有批货
But on this day they're getting a shipment
是从以色列来的打磨好的钻石
of polished stones from lsrael.
他们就象中转站 懂吗?
They're like a way station you know?
- 他们接手后会送往佛蒙特 - 不 不会
- They get picked up and sent to Vermont. - No they're not.
油水怎样 老爹?
What's the cut poppa?
很大 年轻人 非常大
Juicy junior. Real juicy.
听着 伙计 你做你想做的
Look man you do what you want.
我要离开这 老兄 我要找个旅馆呆几天
I'm outta here man. I'm gonna check into a motel for a few days.
我得躲躲 过后再打电话给乔
You know I'll lay low and I'll call Joe- -
该死 他死在我们手上了吗?
Shit. Did he fuckin' die on us?
他是死了还是怎么了?
Huh? ls he dead or what?
- 他没死 - 那是怎么了?
- He ain't dead. - What is it?
他只是昏倒了
I think he's just passed out.
他妈的吓死我了
He scared the fuckin' shit outta me.
我还以为他真的死了
I thought he was dead for sure.
没有医生救治 他真的会死
Without medical attention he will die for sure.
我们该怎么办 老兄? 我们不能送他去医院
What are we gonna do man? We can't take him to the hospital.
没有医生救治 他也许活不过今晚
Without medical attention he might not live through the night.
他中枪是我的错
The bullet in his belly is my fault.
对你来说也许不算什么
While that might not mean jack shit to you
对我来说却很重要
it means a hell of a lot to me.
事有轻重缓急 懂吗? 傻瓜才会留在这 我们得有准备
First things first okay? Stayin' here's goofy. We gotta book up.
那你说该怎么办? 去旅馆?
So what do you suggest we do? Go to a hotel?
我们有个腹部中枪没法走路的人
We got a guy who's shot in the belly
血流得象头中了梭镖的猪
who can't walk bleeds like a stuck pig.
醒来时会痛得大喊大叫
And when he's awake he screams in pain.
你有办法就说
You got an idea spit it out.
乔可以帮忙
Joe could help.
如果我们能联系上乔 乔能给他找个医生
If we could get in touch with Joe Joe could get him to a doctor.
乔能找个医生来看看他
Joe could get a doctor to come to see him.
就算我们可以相信乔 可怎么和他取得联系?
Assuming we can trust Joe how we gonna get in touch with him?
他应该来的 但他没来
He's supposed to be here but he ain't
这让我对留在这感到不安
which makes me nervous about bein' here.
就算他是可靠的
Even if he is on the up and up
我认为他也不会高兴和我们在一起
I don't think he's gonna be too happy with us.
他策划抢劫 结果成了一场屠杀
He planned a robbery and he's got a bloodbath on his hands now.
他得到了死警察 死劫匪 死平民
He's got dead cops dead robbers dead civilians.
我很怀疑 他能对我们表示太多同情
I tend to doubt he's gonna have a lot of sympathy for our plight.
如果我是他 我会尽可能
If I was him I'd put as much distance
让自己离这趟混水远点
between me and this mess as possible.
你到这之前 橙先生...
Before you got here Mr. Orange...
要我送他去医院看医生
was askin' me to take him to a doctor to a hospital.
我不喜欢 这个会把他送到警察手上的主意
I don't like the idea of turnin' him over to the cops...
可我不这样做他就会死
but if we don't he's gonna die.
他求我那样做
He begged me to do it.
好吧 我想我们可以送他去医院
Well all right. Then I guess we take him to a hospital.
他那样说的话 照做好了
If that's what he said let's do it.
既然他不知道我们的底细 就照他说的办
Since he don't know nothin' about us I say it's his decision.
他知道一些我的事
He knows a little about me.
什么? 等等 你跟他说了你的名字吗?
What? Wait wait. You didn't tell him your name did you?
我告诉过他我的名和我从哪来
I told him my first name and where I was from.
为什么?
Why?
几天前我告诉他我是哪里人
I told him where I was from a few days ago.
那只是普通的闲聊
It was just a natural conversation.
你告诉他名字又是为什么?
What was tellin' him your name when you weren't supposed to?
他问的我
He asked.
我们刚摆脱警察时 他中了枪
We had just gotten away from the cops. He just got shot.
他中枪是我的错
It was my fault he got shot.
他浑身都是血
He's a fuckin' bloody mess.
大声尖叫着
He's screamin'.
我发誓我以为他会死在那
I swear to God I thought he was gonna die right then and there.
我想安慰他 告诉他别担心...
I'm tryin' to comfort him telling him not to worry...
一切都会好起来 我会照顾他
everything's going to be okay I'm gonna take care of him.
然后他问我叫什么
And he asked me what my name was.
我是说 他要死在我怀里了
I mean the man was dyin' in my arms.
我他妈的能怎么做?
What the fuck was I supposed to do?
告诉他我很抱歉? 我不能透露这个该死的信息?
Tell him I'm sorry? I can't give out that fuckin' information?
这坏了规矩?
It's against the rules?
我不够信任你?
I don't trust you enough?
也许我该那样做 但我做不到
Maybe I should've but I couldn't.
去你的 去他妈的乔
Fuck you! Fuck Joe!
- 我确信那是个动人的场景 - 别他妈的装腔作势
- I'm sure it was a beautiful scene. - Don't fuckin' patronize me!
我有个问题
I have one question.
警察有你的资料吗?
Do they have a sheet on you where you're from?
- 有 - 那就是了
- Yeah! - That's that then.
我是说 我担心警察会让他辨认你的照片
I mean I was worried about mug shot possibility as it was.
他知道A 你的名字 B 你的相貌 C
He knows A your name B your face C
你的家乡 D 你的专长
your hometown and D your specialty.
他们用不着给他看太多照片
They're not gonna have to show him a lot of pictures
就能把你认出来
for him to pick you out!
你没说别的什么
You didn't tell him anything else
能让警察更容易找出你的资料吧?
so they could narrow down the selection?
如果我不得不再次要你作出让步
If I have to tell you again to back off
我们就会没完没了了
we're gonna go round and round.
我们不能送他去医院
We ain't takin' him to a hospital.
如果不送他去 他会死掉
If we don't he's gonna die.
对此我很难过
And I'm very sad about that
但有人运气好有人运气差
but some fellas are lucky and some ain't.
你他妈的干嘛抓住我?
What the fuck are you touchin' me for man?
让你明白在和谁打交道
I'll show you who you're fuckin' with!
你想向我开枪吗? 来啊 开枪啊
You wanna shoot me you piece of shit?
不是我造成的这个局面 我是在想办法
I didn't create this situation I'm dealin' with it!
你的做法象个刚出道的小毛贼 我的做法才象个行家
You're actin' like a first- year thief! I'm actin' like a professional!
如果警察抓住他 就可能抓到你我...
If they get him they could get you they could get closer to me...
不能让这事发生
and that can't happen!
这难道怪我吗? 我可没告诉他我叫什么
You're lookin' at me like it's my fault? I didn't tell him my name!
也没告诉他我是哪里人
I didn't tell him where I was from!
妈的 十五分钟前你几乎告诉我你叫什么
Shit! Fifteen minutes ago you almost told me your name!
你自己惹的乱子得自己应付
You're gonna get stuck in a situation you created!
如果你想找人发泄 对着镜子发泄好了
So if you wanna throw bad looks around throw 'em at a mirror!
你们不该表现得这样粗鲁
You kids shouldn't play so rough.
有人要开始哭了
Somebody's gonna start cryin'.
金先生
Mr. Blonde.
你他妈的踢了我
Shit. You're fuckin' kickin' me.
你出了什么状况? 还以为你死了呢
What happened to you? Figured you were dead.
嘿 你没事吧?
Hey you okay?
你知道蓝的下落吗?
Did you see what happened to Blue?
我们不知道你们出了什么问题
We didn't know what happened to you.
这是我们想知道的
That's what we were wonderin' about.
听着 褐已经死了 橙腹部中了枪
Look Brown is dead Orange got it in the belly.
够了 够了
Enough! Enough!
你最好快说 混蛋
You better start talkin' asshole.
因为我们还有要紧的事要说
'Cause we got shit we need to talk about.
我们已经绞尽脑汁
We're already freaked out.
我们需要你加入来帮我们弄清楚
We need you actin' freaky like we need a fuckin' bag on our hip.
好吧 让我们谈谈
Okay let's talk.
我们认为在这房子里有个内奸
We think we got a rat in the house.
我肯定我们当中有个内奸
I guarantee we got a rat in the house.
你为什么这样说?
What makes you say that?
那样想很有趣吗?
Is that supposed to be funny?
听着 我们觉得这地方不安全
Look we think this place ain't safe.
这儿不再安全
This place ain't secure anymore.
你该和我们一起离开
We're leavin' and you should go with us.
谁都别想离开
Nobody's goin' anywhere.
去他的臭狗屎
Piss on this fuckin' turd.
- 我们离开这 - 别再走一步 白先生
- We're outta here. - Don't take another step Mr. White.
去你妈的 疯子
Fuck you maniac!
我们身处困境都他妈怪你
It's your fuckin' fault we're in this trouble!
这家伙有什么问题?
What's this guy's problem?
我有什么问题? 对 我有个见鬼的问题
What's my problem? Yeah I got a fuckin' problem!
我有个该死的大问题...
I got a big fuckin' problem...
就是和一个胡乱开枪 几乎将我干掉的疯子在一起
with any trigger- happy madman who almost gets me shot!
- 你他妈的在说什么? - 说你那该死的疯狂射击
- What the fuck you talkin' about? - That fucking shooting spree!
在那个店里 记得吗?
In the store! Remember?
哦 去他妈的 他们启动了报警装置 他们活该
Oh fuck 'em. They set off the alarm. They deserve what they got.
你几乎杀了我
You almost killed me!
混蛋
Asshole!
如果我早知道你这么疯
If I knew what kind of guy you were
我绝不会同意和你共事
I never would've agreed to work with you.
小狗 你要吠上一整天...
Are you gonna bark all day little doggie...
还是要咬人?
or are you gonna bite?
你说什么?
What was that?
对不起 我没听清 你能再说一次吗?
I'm sorry I didn't catch it. Would you repeat it?
你想叫上一整天 小狗...
Are you gonna bark all day little doggie...
还是想咬人?
or are you gonna bite?
你们两个混蛋 他妈的冷静点 别这样
You two assholes calm the fuck down! Hey come on!
我们难道是在角斗场吗? 我是唯一的专业人士吗?
What are we on a playground here? Am I the only professional?
你们的举止就象两个他妈的黑鬼
You're actin' like a bunch of fuckin' niggers!
跟黑鬼合作过吗?
Ever work with niggers? Always sayin
他们总说要干掉对方
they're gonna kill each other.
你说过想把他干掉
You said yourself you thought about taking him out.
- 你他妈的那样说过? - 对 那又怎么样?
- You fuckin' said that? - Yeah I did okay?
但那是之前 现在
But that was then. Right now
这家伙是我唯一信得过的人
this guy is the only one I completely trust.
- 对付警察时他最狠 - 你站在他那边?
- He's too homicidal to be with the cops. - You takin' his side?
去他妈的立场 老兄 我们现在需要团结
Fuck sides man! What we need here is solidarity!
有人用烧红的火钳捅我们的屁股
Somebody's stickin' a red- hot poker up our ass
我要把他找出来
and I want to know who.
妈的 听着 我知道我不是内奸
Fuck. Look I know I'm no piece of shit.
我十分肯定你没问题
I'm pretty sure you're okay
我他妈的也相信你没问题
and I'm fuckin' positive you're on the level.
所以让我们仔细想想谁是内奸 行吗?
So let's try and figure out who the bad guy is all right?
这真是令人兴奋
Wow. That was really exciting.
我打赌你是李·马文的拥趸 对吗?
I bet you're a big Lee Marvin fan aren't ya?
我也是 我喜欢那家伙
Yeah me too. I love that guy.
我的心跳很快 几乎心脏病发
My heart's beatin' so fast I'm about to have a heart attack here.
我有些东西在外面
I got somethin' outside that
我想让你们看看 跟我来
I'd like to show you guys so follow me.
跟你去? 去哪?
Follow you? Where?
去我的车
To my car.
你忘了你的薯条和汽水吗?
Did you forget your French fries to go with the soda?
不 我已经吃过了
No I had them already.
有些东西我觉得你们没准想看看
I got somethin' I think you might wanna see though.
- 是什么? - 一个大惊喜
- What? - It's a big surprise.
我肯定你会喜欢它 来吧
I'm sure you'll like it. Come on.
我们还是离开这吧
We still gotta get outta here you know.
不 我们得留下继续等
No. We're gonna stick around and we're gonna wait.
- 等什么? 警察吗? - 不 是等"好家伙"艾迪
- What for? The cops? - No. Nice Guy Eddie.
"好家伙"艾迪? 你怎么认为
Nice Guy Eddie? What makes you think
他不是在去哥斯达黎加的飞机上呢?
he isn't on a plane halfway to Costa Rica?
因为我和他通过电话
Because I spoke to him on the phone
他说他在来这的路上
and he said he's on the way down here.
你和"好家伙"艾迪谈过?
You talked to Nice Guy Eddie?
为什么你不早说?
Why didn't you say that in the first place?
- 你没问过我 - 非常幽默
- 'Cause you never asked me. - Hardy- fuckin'- har.
- 他怎么说? - 他说留在原地
- What'd he say? - He said stay put.
这段时间里...
So in the meantime...
我会给你们看点东西
I'll show you guys somethin'.
老天
Jesus Christ.
也许我们穿制服的朋友 可以回答一些...
Maybe our boy in blue here can answer some of these questions...
你们讨论过的有关内奸的问题
about this rat business you've been talkin' about.
真有你的 伙计
You're a piece of work my friend.
让我们把他妈的弄出来
Let's get him the fuck outta here.
金先生
嘿 你能放松点吗?
Hey Sid will you relax?
我认识你很长时间了 我不会担心
I've known you a long time. I'm not worried.
我知道你会报答我
I know you'll pay me back.
别跟我说我早就知道的东西 别让我尴尬
Don't tell me what I already know. Don't embarrass me.
你有几个月过得很糟 过得和别人没什么两样
So you had a few bad months. You do what everybody else does.
我不在乎什么J.P.摩根或者欧文裁缝 你已经渡过难关了
I don't care if it's J.P. Morgan or lrving the tailor. You ride it out.
- 维克·维加在外面 - 等等
- Vic Vega's outside. - Hold on.
- 谁? - 维克·维加
- Who? - Vic Vega.
叫他进来.我得挂了
Tell him to come in. I gotta go.
- 进来吧 - 有个朋友在等我
- Come on in. - A friend of mine's outside.
我会和你谈的 别担心
I'll be talkin' to you. Don't worry.
嘿 欢迎回来 维克
Hey welcome home Vic.
自由的感觉怎么样 嗯?
How does freedom feel huh?
- 全都不同了 - 没那么悲观
- It's a change. - Ain't that the sad truth.
坐下 脱掉你的外套 别客气
Sit down take your coat off make yourself at home.
- 要喝一杯吗? - 好的
- Have a little drink? - Yeah.
小雷蒙·马丁怎么样?
How about a little Remy Martin?
行
Sure.
你的假释官是谁?
Who's your parole officer?
西摩斯·斯盖里提
Seymour Scagnetti.
他怎么样?
How is he?
是个该死的混蛋 竟然不许我离开房子半步
He's a fuckin' asshole. Won't even let me leave the halfway house.
真让我惊诧不已
It never ceases to amaze me.
一个为了二十五美分
A fuckin' jungle bunny goes out
割破女人喉咙的小乖乖给放了出来
there slits a woman's throat for 25 cents...
却得整天和假释官呆在一起
he gets Doris Day for a parole officer.
一个象你这样的好小伙子 却和一个混蛋纠缠不清
A good fella like you winds up with a ball- bustin' prick.
我想让你知道我很感激
I want you to know I appreciate all
坐牢时你给我送的东西
the packages you sent me on the inside.
我能怎么样呢?
What the hell was I supposed to do?
把你忘了?
Forget about you?
我只想让你知道 那对我来说意味着很多
I just want you to know that it meant a lot to me.
那是我起码能做到的 我希望能做得更多
It was the least I could do. I wish to hell I could've done a lot more.
非常感谢 乔
Thanks a lot Joe.
啊 维克
Ah Vic.
牙签维克
Toothpick Vic.
跟我说说你的故事 孩子 你有什么打算?
So tell me your story kid. What are your plans?
你这狗娘养的 真不敢相信是你坐在那
You son of a bitch. I see you sittin' there but I don't believe it.
- 你怎么样 牙签? - 嘿 艾迪
- How you doin' Toothpick? - Hey Eddie.
听着 我很抱歉 我该亲自去接你的
Listen I'm sorry. I should've picked you up myself.
我...我他妈的- - 这礼拜太疯狂了
I was... My fuckin'...This week's been crazy.
我忙得头都挨着屁股了
I've had my head up my ass the whole time.
你的话很有趣
Funny you say that cause that's
我和你爸爸正在说这事
what me and your daddy were talkin' about.
是说我该亲自去接你吗?
That I should've picked you up?
是说你头挨着屁股
No that you had your head up your ass.
我一来 他象在说:"维克...
I walk in the door he's like "Vic Vic...
"真高兴 总算有个知道该怎么做的人来了
I'm so glad somebody's finally here who knows what's goin' on.
"我儿子艾迪是个糊涂蛋
My son Eddie's a fuck- up.
"他只会毁了这些生意
He's ruining the business.
"我是说 我爱这家伙
I mean I love the guy
但他做的每件事都一塌糊涂"
but he's flushin' everything down the toilet."
那是你说的对吗? 乔 你自己告诉他
That's what you said right Joe? Tell him yourself.
艾迪 我讨厌你听到这些
Eddie I hate for you to hear it like this...
但维克进来问我生意怎么样
but Vic came in and asked me how business was.
你不能对一个 在监狱里呆了四年的家伙说谎
You don't lie to a guy who's just done four years in the slammer.
就是这样
That's very true.
好了 闹够了 歇歇吧
All right enough of this shit! Break it up!
好了 这不是角斗场
Come on this ain't a playground!
想在地上打滚就去艾迪的办公室
You guys wanna roll around on the floor
别在我这胡闹
you do it in Eddie's office not mine.
- 老爹 看到没有? - 什么?
- Daddy did you see that? - What?
他把我按在地上想操我
The guy got me on the ground he tried to fuck me.
- 你求之不得 - 你这变态混蛋 维克
- You wish. - You sick bastard Vic.
你想在我老爹的办公室操我
You tried to fuck me in my father's office.
听着 维克
Look Vic
不管你想在自己家干什么私事...
whatever you wanna do in the privacy of your own home...
尽管做 但别想操我
go to it but don't try to fuck me.
我可不会考虑你的好意
I don't think of you that way.
我很喜欢你 伙计 但我不会让你那样做
I like you a lot buddy but I don't think of you that way.
听着 如果我是个操屁眼的牛仔
Listen if I was a butt cowboy
我不会把你扔给那些暴徒
I wouldn't even throw you to the posse.
不 你不会 你会把我留给你自己
No you wouldn't. You'd keep me for yourself.
操了四年的屁股
Four years fuckin' punks up the ass
你肯定会对一个漂亮的身体感兴趣
you'd appreciate a piece of prime rib.
我可以撕碎你 "好家伙"
I might break you in Nice Guy
但我会让你和狗做性伴侣
but I'd make you my dog's bitch.
真可悲是吧? 老爹
Ain't that a sad sight Daddy?
进监狱时是白人
A man walks into prison a white man
出来后说话却象个黑鬼
walks out talkin' like a fuckin' nigger.
知道是为什么? 大概是那些黑人的精液...
You know what? I think it's all that black semen...
从你屁眼灌进你脑子里了
pumped up your asshole now it's backed into your fuckin' brain...
而且还会从你嘴里流出来
and it's comin' out your mouth!
艾迪 你再象母狗一样说话
Eddie you keep talkin' like a bitch
我就会象对付母狗那样抽你
I'm gonna slap you like a bitch.
够了 真让我恶心
Enough of that shit! I'm sick of it!
现在你俩都坐下
Now both of you sit down.
艾迪..
Now Eddie...
你进来的时候我们在谈正事
when you came in here we were talkin' some serious business.
维克的假释官有点麻烦
Vic here's got a parole problem.
- 谁是你的假释官? - 西摩斯·斯盖里提
- Who's your P.O.? - Seymour Scagnetti.
斯盖里提 妈的
Scagnetti. Fuck.
- 我听说他是个混蛋 - 他就是个混蛋
- I hear he's a motherfucker. - Oh he's a fucker.
在我找到什么狗屁工作前
Won't even let me leave the halfway house
甚至不许离开住所半步
unless I get some shitty job.
你会回来替我们工作 对吗?
You're comin' back to work for us right?
我想回来
Well I wanna.
但我首先要向那猪脑子证明...
But first I gotta prove to uh ass- head...
我能找到一份象模象样的正式工作
that I can get a regular you know job- type job...
在我能自由行动之前
before I can move out on my own.
如果我得为此操心 我就不能回来替你们做事
I can't come back to work for you guys if I gotta worry about uh...
还有每天晚上十点...
makin' some silly- ass 10:00 curfew...
愚蠢的熄灯禁制
every fuckin' night.
我们能解决这些问题 是吧 艾迪?
We can work this out can't we Eddie?
并不太难办
This ain't all that bad.
我们可以给你找很多合法工作
We can get you a lot of legitimate jobs.
我会让你去长滩做码头工人
I'll get you down in Long Beach as a dockworker.
我可不想做他妈的搬运工 艾迪
I don't wanna lift no fuckin' crates Eddie.
你不用搬什么东西 你甚至不用干活
You ain't gonna lift shit. You don't even work there.
至于档案所记录的 是你在工作
But as far as the records are concerned you do.
我会给马修电话告诉他有个新人
I call Matthews and tell him he's got a new guy boom
你会在安排表上
you're on the rotation.
你会有一张卡记录你每天的出入时间
You get a time card. It's clocked in and out for you every day.
到了周末你会拿到一份不错的薪水
At the end of the week you get a nice paycheck.
码头工人很不赖
Dockworkers do very well.
你能搬进一个象样的地方
You can move into a halfway decent place
不会有斯盖里提问...
without Scagnetti goin'...
"这些钱是他妈从哪来的? "
"Where the fuck's the money comin' from? "
另外 如果他决定做一次突然来访...
And if he decides to make a surprise visit...
我们就说派你去塔斯廷搬东西了
that's the day we sent you to Tustin to pick up a load of shit.
如果他再来 嘿 抱歉 西摩斯
If he comes back again hey "Sorry Seymour.
"你错过他了
You just missed him.
我们派他去塔夫托机场 要工作五小时
We had to send him to the Taft airstrip five fuckin' hours away.
"我们要他去提货然后带回这"
We had a load of shit he had to pick up there and bring back here."
你的工作决定你得到处跑 这是个漂亮的安排
Part of your job is goin' different places. That's the beauty of it.
我们到处都有生意
We got places all over the place.
懂了吗? 我说过不用担心
See Vic? Did I tell you not to worry?
- 维克曾担心过 - 我明天带你去长滩
- Vic was worried. - I'll take you to Long Beach tomorrow.
我们会向马修介绍你 告诉他如此这般
We'll get you fixed up with Matthews I'll tell him what's what.
要知道 我真的很感激你们的安排
You know I really appreciate what you guys are doin'...
但我想知道我什么时候能回来
but I'd like to know when I can come back...
做些真正的工作
you know do some real work.
这可很难说
Well it's hard to say.
这是个特殊时刻
It's kind of a strange time now.
事情有点...
Things are kind of...
有点混乱 就是这样
They're a little fucked up is what they are.
我们要筹备在维加斯的一个大聚会
We're just gettin' ready for a big meetin' right now in Vegas.
听着 现在先让艾迪安排你去长滩
Look just let Eddie for now set you up at Long Beach.
给你找个工作 一些现金
Get you a job give you some cash...
让那个斯盖里提从你背后滚开
and get this Scagnetti fuck off your back...
然后我们再跟你谈 行吗?
and then we'll talk to you all right?
老爹 我有个主意
Huh? Dad I got an idea.
听我说
Just hear me out.
我知道你 不喜欢用自己的手下做那些事
I know you don't like usin' the boys on these jobs...
但维克在这 我是说 他什么都没做过却能给我们带来好运
but Vic here...I mean he's only been nothin' but good luck for us.
这家伙绝不会抱怨叫苦
The guy's a fuckin' rabbit's foot for cryin' out loud.
我希望他能加入
I'd like to have him in.
你知道他能控制自己
You know he can handle himself
而且你肯定可以信任他
and you damn sure know you can trust him.
好吧 维克
All right Vic...
你觉得和另外五个人 合作干一票买卖怎么样?
how would you feel about pullin' a job with about five other guys?
我感觉非常棒
I'd feel great about it.
K·比利的"70年代超级声"继续播出
K·BILLY's "Super Sounds of the '70s" continues.
如果你是第十二个来电者...
If you're the 12th caller...
你将赢得两张今晚卡逊游乐场...
you'll win two tickets to the monster truck extravaganza...
怪兽卡车滑稽剧的入场劵
being held tonight at the Carson Fairgrounds...
出演者是大爹东- 邦迪的卡车"巨兽"
featuring Big Daddy Don Bodine's truck "The Behemoth."
请获奖者到电台领奖
The 12th caller wins on the station where the '70s survived.
嘿 达夫 我们的情况不妙
Hey Dov we got a major situation here.
相信你也知道
I know you know that.
我得问问老爹看他想怎么做
I gotta talk to Daddy and find out what he wants done.
我知道的消息全来自维克
All I know is what Vic told me.
那地方变成了战场
The place turned into a bullet- fest.
他胁持了一个警察逃了出来
He took a cop hostage just to get the fuck outta there.
起来 起来
Get up! Get up!
我象他妈的在开玩笑吗?
Do I sound like I'm fuckin' jokin'?
他把一个警察 锁在行李箱里驾车逃跑了
He's fuckin' drivin' around with a cop in his trunk!
我不知道谁做了什么
I don't know who did what!
不知道谁拿了货
I don't know who's got the loot.
不知道是否有人拿到了货
I don't know if anybody's got the loot.
不知道谁死谁活 谁被抓了谁没被抓
I don't know who's dead who's alive who's caught who's not.
我会知道的 我现在快到那了
I will know. I'm practically there now.
可我怎么告诉他们老爹是什么想法?
But what do I tell these guys about Daddy?
好吧 你肯定他是那样说的?
All right. You sure that's what he said?
好吧 我会那样对他们说
Okay that's what I'll tell 'em.
嗯? 去你妈的
Huh? Fuck you!
你喜欢做他妈的英雄? 你想做他妈的英雄?
You like bein' a fuckin' hero? You like bein' a fuckin' hero?
你高兴做英雄?
You like bein' a fuckin' hero?
你会白白受苦 伙计
You're gonna suffer for nothin' pal.
你听到了吗? 你得他妈的说出来
You hear me? 'Cause you're gonna fuckin' talk.
- 我什么都不知道 - 你他妈的知道
- I don't fucking know anything! - You fuckin' know.
你知道的 看着我 你他妈的知道
You know. Look at me. You fuckin' know.
这到底怎么回事?
What in the Sam Hill's goin' on here?
- "好家伙" 我们抓到了一个警察 - 他妈的乔在哪?
- Nice Guy we got a cop. - Where the fuck is Joe?
我的天 橙死了
Holy shit. Orange is dead.
不 他没死 只是得不到照顾就会死
No he's not dead but he will be if we don't get him taken care of.
我们中了埋伏 警察早就在那
We were set up. The cops were there waitin' for us.
什么? 没有谁出卖任何人
What? Nobody fuckin' set anybody up.
警察在那等着我们
The cops were there waitin' for us.
- 胡说 - 去你的
- Bullshit. - Fuck you man!
你没在那 我们在 警察早就监视了店子
You weren't there we were and the cops had that store staked out.
好了 该死的侦探先生 你真他妈的聪明
Okay Mr. Fuckin' Detective you're so fuckin' smart.
- 是谁干的? - 我们早就互相问过
- Who did it? - We've been askin' each other!
那你什么意思? 你以为是我他妈的出卖了你们?
What'd you come up with? You think I fuckin' set you up?
不知道 但总有这么个人
I don't know but somebody did.
没人干过 你们这些混蛋把珠宝店变成了...
Nobody did. You fuckin' assholes turned the jewelry store...
- 不许你叫我混蛋 - 你他妈的白痴
- Don't you call me an asshole! - You fuckin' idiot!
在那上演西部片
Turned the jewelry store into a wild west show...
还问为什么警察会出现?
and you wonder why the fuckin' cops show up?
约瑟夫在哪?
Where's Joseph?
不知道 我没和他通过话
I don't know. I ain't talked to him.
我和达夫谈过
I talked to Dov.
他说老爹火冒三丈正在赶来
He says Daddy's comin'down here and he's fuckin' pissed.
他很恼火? 我说过他会
He's pissed? I told you he'd be pissed.
乔怎么说?
What'd Joe say?
我说了我没跟他通过话
I told you I ain't talked to him!
- 只知道他很恼火 - 你想拿他怎么办?
- All I know is he's pissed. - What are you gonna do about him?
让我他妈的喘口气
Give me a fuckin'chance to breathe.
我自己也有几个问题
I got a few questions of my own here.
你不会死 他会
You ain't dying. He is.
好吧 他妈的慈悲先生 我会打电话找人
All right Mr. Fuckin' Compassion I will call somebody!
找谁?
Who?
你以为是找杂技演员吗? 当然是找医生
A fuckin' snake charmer! Who do you think? I'll call a doctor.
他们会治好他 褐和蓝怎么样?
They'll fix him right up. What happened to Brown and Blue?
褐死了 蓝不知下落
Brown's dead. We don't know what happened to Blue.
褐死了? 你肯定?
Brown's dead? Are you sure?
我肯定 我当时在那 他头上中了一枪
I'm sure. I was there. He took one in the head.
没人知道蓝先生怎么样吗?
Nobody's got a clue what happened to Mr. Blue?
也不知道他是死是活
Either he's alive or he's dead...
是被警察抓了还是没被抓
or the cops got him or they don't.
我得从这杂种嘴里问出来
I take it this is the bastard you told me about.
你们干嘛揍他?
Why are you beatin' on him?
也许他能说出谁是内奸
Maybe he could tell us who set us up.
你继续揍这杂种
If you fuckin'beat this prick long enough
他会告诉你芝加哥大火是他干的
he'll tell you he started the Chicago Fire.
这不会有多大用处
Now that don't necessarily make it fuckin' so!
拜托 伙计 用用脑子
Come on man think!
好了 最后一件要紧事
All right first things fuckin' last.
谁拿了钻石?
Who's got the stones?
拜托 有谁能告诉我一点线索?
Please somebody tell me one little fuckin' favor.
在我手里
I got a bag.
满意了吗? 我藏起来了
Okay? I stashed it 'til
我得先确定这地方还没变成警局
we could be sure this place wasn't a police station.
很好 我们现在去拿吧
Good for you. Now let's go get it.
首先我们得处理那些车
First we gotta get rid of those cars.
外面看起来就象停车场
It looks like Sam's Hot Car Lot outside.
好吧
Okay.
金留在这照看他们两个
Blondie stay here and baby- sit them two.
白和粉各开一辆车
White and Pink take a car each.
我跟在你们后面 扔掉车之后去取钻石
I'll follow you. You ditch 'em. Pick up the stones.
我会在路上
While I'm followin' you
替我们的朋友安排一个医生
I'll arrange some sort of a doctor for our friend.
不能让他和这家伙在一起
You can't leave these guys here with him.
- 为什么? - 因为他是个该死的疯子
- Why not? - Because he's a fuckin' psycho.
如果你觉得乔很恼火...
And if you think Joe's pissed off...
那绝对比不上我对于让我...
that ain't nothin' compared to how pissed off I am at him...
和这杂种呆在一块火大
for puttin' me in the same room as that bastard.
看到我都忍受了些什么吗? 艾迪
You see what I've been puttin' up with Eddie?
我他妈的走进来让这些家伙留下来
I fuckin' walked in here I told these guys about stayin' put.
白先生掏出枪来指着我的脸
Mr. White whips out his gun he's stickin' it in my face...
叫我混蛋 说他要干掉我
callin' me a motherfucker sayin' he's gonna blow me away...
然后不停地说废话
and blah blah blah blah blah.
是他让行动变成了射击派对
He's the reason the joint turned into a shootin' spree.
你他妈的哑巴了?
What are you a fuckin' silent partner?
告诉他
Tell him!
他在店子里发疯 但现在看来很正常
He went crazy in the store but he seems all right now.
他当时做的就是...
This is what he was doin': bam bam...
没错
Yeah bam bam bam bam bam.
我叫他们别碰该死的报警器 可他们不听
I told 'em not to touch the fuckin' alarm they did.
如果他们照我说的做
If they hadn't have done what I told 'em not to do
他们就不会死
they'd still be alive.
他妈的英雄
My fuckin' hero.
谢谢
Thanks.
那就是你疯狂大屠杀的借口?
That's your excuse for going on a kill- crazy rampage?
我不喜欢报警器 白先生
I don't like alarms Mr. White.
谁留下来看着这个警察有什么关系?
What does it matter who stays with the cop?
不能放他走 他能认出我们
We ain't lettin' him go. He's seen everybody.
我谁也没看见
I haven't been looking at you guys.
他妈的闭嘴 伙计
Shut the fuck up man!
关键在于 不该把他
You guys should never have taken him
从行李箱弄出来
outta the trunk in the first place.
- 我们想找出谁是内奸 - 没有什么他妈的内奸
- We tried to find out about the setup. - There is no fuckin' setup!
现在听我说
Now here's the news!
金 你留下来照看他们两个
Blondie you stay here take care of these two!
白和粉 和我一起走 如果乔...
White and Pink you come with me 'cause if Joe gets here...
看到外面停着那么多车
and he sees all these cars parked outside...
我发誓他对谁都不会有什么好脸色
I swear to you he's gonna be just as mad at me as he is at you.
没问题 我们走吧
Fine. Let's go.
总算清静了
Alone at last.
猜猜怎么着
Guess what.
我想我把车停在禁区了
I think I'm parked in the red zone.
我们说到哪了?
Now where were we?
我告诉你 我对他妈的内奸一无所知
I told you I don't know anything about any fuckin' setup.
我加入警队只有八个月
I've been on the force for only eight months.
他们不会告诉我任何事
They don't tell me anything.
没人跟我说过 你用尽方法折磨我也没用
Nobody tells me shit. You can torture me all you want.
折磨你? 好主意
Torture you? That's a good...
这是个好主意 我喜欢它
That's a good idea. I like that one yeah.
你的老板都说了没什么内奸
Even your boss said there wasn't a setup.
- 我的什么? - 你的老板
- My what? - Your boss.
抱歉 伙计
Excuse me pal.
有件事你得弄明白 我没什么老板
One thing I wanna make clear to you: I don't have a boss.
没人能对我指手划脚 懂吗?
Nobody tells me what to do. You understand?
听到我的话了吗? 狗娘养的
You hear what I said you son of a bitch?
好的 好的 好的 你没有老板
All right all right all right you don't have a boss.
他妈的真够脏
Get that fuckin' shit off.
听着 我不会再跟你废话 明白吗?
Look I'm not gonna bullshit you okay?
我不会真的在乎你知道还是不知道
I don't really give a good fuck what you know or don't know...
但我会折磨你
but I'm gonna torture you anyway...
不管怎样
regardless.
不是为了要知道什么
Not to get information.
只是为了寻开心...
It's amusing to me...
而折磨一个警察
to torture a cop.
你想说什么都行 因为我早都听过了
You can say anything you want because I've heard it all before.
你能做的只有...
All you can do is...
祈求快点死去...
pray for a quick death...
总之...
which...
你将求死不能
you ain't gonna get.
天啊
Oh God.
你听过K·比利的"70年代超级声"吗?
You ever listen to K·BILLY's "Super Sounds of the '70s"?
那是我最喜欢的节目
It's my personal favorite.
艾根和莱佛蒂象"偷来的车轮"一样
Joe Egan and Gerry Rafferty were
是知名的歌唱组合
a duo known as Stealer's Wheel...
他们录制 "最爱泡泡糖"这张专辑时...
when they recorded this Dylanesque pop bubble- gum favorite...
是1974年四月
from April of 1974.
曾升到排行榜第五位...
That reached up to number five...
就象七零年代 在"70年代超级声"的延续
as K- BILLY's "Super Sounds of the '70s" continues.
别动
Hold still.
别动 该死的
Hold still you fuck.
这也没什么不好是吗?
Was that good for you too?
嘿 怎么回事?
Hey what's goin' on?
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
哪也别去 我就会回来
Don't go anywhere. I'll be right back.
别 停下 停下
Don't! Stop! Stop!
- 什么? 怎么了? - 别这么做
- What? What's the matter? - Don't do this.
那么就烧一点点?
That burn a little bit?
不 停下
Don't! Stop!
求求你停下
Please stop.
停下 停下
Just stop. Stop.
我跟你说 别 求你了
Just talk to me. Don't. Please.
别烧我 求你了
Don't burn me please.
我对你们一无所知
I don't know anything about any of you fucking guys.
我什么都不会说
I'm not gonna say anything.
不 求你了 不
No! Please no.
- 你说完了吗? - 停下
- You all through? - Stop!
说完了吗?
You all through?
求你了 我家里还有个孩子
Please. I got a little kid at home.
完了吗?
You all done?
- 不要 - 点火了
- Don't! - Have some fire.
哦 妈的
Oh shit.
嘿 你
Hey you.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
马文
Marvin.
马文什么?
Marvin what?
马文·纳什
Marvin Nash.
听着 马文 我是...
Listen to me Marvin. I'm a- -
听我说 马文·纳什 我是警察
Listen to me Marvin Nash. I'm a cop.
是的 我知道
Yeah I know.
你知道?
You do?
是的 你叫弗雷蒂什么的
Yeah. Your name's Freddy somethin'.
纽文狄克
Newendyke.
弗雷蒂·纽文狄克
Freddy Newendyke.
弗兰克·费切蒂...
Frankie Ferchetti...
大概五个月前向我们介绍过
introduced us about five months ago.
我记不太清了
I don't remember that at all.
我记得
I do.
弗雷蒂
Freddy.
我成什么样了?
How do I look?
怎么?
What?
我不知该怎么对你说 马文
I don't know what to tell you Marvin.
那个该死的
That fuck.
那该死的变态
That sick fuck!
那该死的杂种
That fuckin' bastard!
马文 你得撑住
Marvin I need you to hold on.
警察一直在另一个街区等候行动
There's cops waiting to move a block away.
他们在他妈的等什么?
What the fuck are they waiting for?
这个该死的家伙 他弄伤了我的脸
This fuckin' guy he slashes my face...
还他妈的割掉了我的耳朵
and cuts my fuckin' ear off!
我他妈的被毁了容
I'm fuckin' deformed!
去你妈的
Fuck you!
我他妈的都快死了
I'm fuckin' dyin' here!
我他妈的要死了
I'm fuckin' dyin'!
在乔·卡伯特出现之前他们不会行动
They're not to make a move 'til Joe Cabot shows up.
我是被派来抓他的
I was sent in to get him.
懂吗?
All right?
你也听到了 他正在赶来
You heard 'em. They said he's on his way.
别对我发火 马文
Don't pussy out on me now Marvin.
我们只要呆在这继续流血...
We're just gonna sit here and bleed...
等乔·卡伯特 把他那该死的脑袋伸进来
'til Joe Cabot sticks his fuckin' head through that door.
橙先生
向这个"自己人"问好吧
Say hello to a motherfucker who's inside.
卡伯特接了个买卖 他想要我加入
Cabot's doing a job. He wants me on the team.
这最好不是个玩笑
This better not be a joke.
不是玩笑 我混进去了 取得了他的信任
This ain't a joke. I'm in. I'm up his ass.
"好家伙"艾迪告诉我乔想见我
Nice Guy Eddie tells me Joe wants to meet me.
他让我等一个电话
He says I should just wait for a phone call.
等了三天后
After waiting three days
昨晚他打电话给我说乔准备好了
he calls me last night and says Joe's ready.
- 他十五分钟后来接我 - 谁接的你?
- He'll pick me up in 15 minutes. - Who picked you up?
- "好家伙" 我们去了一家酒吧 - 哪家?
- Nice Guy. We get to a bar. - What bar?
皮特开的那家
Smokey Pete's in Gardena.
我们到了那...
We get there...
见到乔和一个叫白先生的人
and I meet Joe and a guy named Mr. White.
是假名 我叫橙先生
Phony name. My name's Mr. Orange.
- 橙先生? - 橙先生
- Mr. Orange? - Mr. Orange.
那么 橙先生
Okay Mr. Orange.
- 你以前从没见过那混蛋? - 谁? 白先生吗?
- You ever see this motherfucker before? - Who? Mr. White?
对 白先生
Yes. Mr. White.
不 他不是卡伯特的手下
No. He ain't one of Cabot's men either.
他是从外地来的
He's gotta be from out of town.
- 乔和他很熟 - 你怎么能断定?
- Joe knows him good. - How can you tell?
从他们说话的样子能断定他们是朋友
The way they talk. You can tell they're buddies.
- 你们聊过吗? - 我和乔吗?
- You two talk? - Me and Joe?
白先生
Mr. White.
- 一点点 - 说些什么?
- A little. - About what?
- "酿酒者" - "密尔沃基酿酒者"队?
The Brewers. Milwaukee Brewers?
他们头天晚上赢了比赛 他赢了些钱
They won the night before. He made some money off them.
很好 如果他是"酿酒者"队的球迷 他就是从威斯康辛来的
Good. If this crook's a Brewers fan he's gotta be from Wisconsin.
我敢和你打赌...
And I'll bet you everything...
密尔沃基肯定有这个白先生的资料
they got a sheet in Milwaukee on this Mr. White's ass.
所以我想要你去看看密尔沃基的档案
So I want you to go through everybody in Milwaukee...
看看所有有关武装抢劫的资料 找出他的名字
with a history of armed robbery and put a name to the face.
- 干得不错 弗雷蒂 - 谢谢 伙计
- Nice work Freddy. - Thank you my man.
- 麦克那个人怎么样? - 不错
- How was Long Beach Mike's referral? - Perfect.
他一直都在帮我
His backing me up went a long way.
我跟他们说我俩是牌友
I told them I played poker with him.
"好家伙"调查过之后说没问题
Nice Guy checked it out and said it was A- okay.
说我是个在行的盗贼 我没多说什么
Said I was a good thief I didn't rattle...
然后我开始准备行动
and that I was ready to move.
他是个好人 没他我混不进去
He's a good guy. I wouldn't be inside without him.
不 不 不...
No no no
长滩麦克不是你的朋友
Long Beach Mike is not your friend.
长滩麦克是个他妈的人渣
Long Beach Mike is a fucking scumbag.
他出卖了他的朋友
He's selling out his friends.
他就是那种好法
That's how nice he fuckin' is.
我会小心他的
I'll take care of his ass...
你做事的时候要注意撇开那个下流坯
but you get that scumbag out of mind and take care of business.
我是这样做的
Gone.
用那个"马桶故事"吗?
Use the commode story?
- 什么"马桶故事"? - 是个电影情节 记住它
- What's the commode story? - It's a scene. Memorize it.
- 是什么? - 做卧底就要象白兰度
- A what? - Undercover cops gotta be Brando.
得做个好演员 表现得自然逼真
To do this job you gotta be a great actor naturalistic.
要表现得无懈可击
You gotta be naturalistic as hell.
如果你是个糟糕的演员 事情就会干砸了
If you're a bad actor that's bullshit in this job.
什么乱七八糟的?
What is this?
是关于毒品交易的趣事
That's an amusing anecdote about a drug deal.
当你工作时
Something funny that
发生的一些趣事
happened to you while you were doing a job.
我要全记住吗? 这些狗屁足有四页
I gotta memorize all this? There's four pages of this shit.
就当它是个笑话
Think about it like it's a joke.all right?
记住最重要的 其余的你看着办
Memorize what's important. The rest you make your own.all right?
- 你会讲笑话对吧?  - 不会
- You can tell a joke can't you? - No
就当你是东·瑞科斯在说笑话 行吗?
Well pretend you're Don Rickles... and tell a joke all right?
关键是你要记住细节
The things you gotta remember are the details.
这对你的故事有帮助
The details sell your story.
故事场景是在一间男厕所
This particular story takes place in a men's room.
你得知道所有的细节
You gotta know all the details...
不管他们用纸巾还是暖风机把手弄干
whether they got paper towels or a blower to dry your hands.
你得知道隔间是否有门
You gotta know if the stalls ain't got no doors or not.
得知道是否有透明皂
You gotta know if they got liquid soap
或者粉红色的狗屁颗粒...
or that pink granulated shit...
那种中学里用的东西
they used in high school.
你得知道是否有热水 臭不臭...
You gotta know if they got hot water or not if it stinks...
脏不脏 是否有缺德的杂种...
if some nasty lowlife scum- ridden motherfucker...
拉肚子弄得马桶上到处都是
sprayed diarrhea all over one of the bowls.
你得知道有关马桶的每个细节
You gotta know every detail there is to know about this commode.
你得告诉他们这些全是你的经历
What you gotta do is take all them details and make 'em your own.
你这样做的时候 想要记住这是你的故事...
While you're doing that remember that this story is about you...
和你是怎么接受这些事情的
and how you perceived the events that went down.
唯一的办法就是...
The only way to do that...
不停地说它
is keep sayin' it...
一遍又一遍地说
and sayin' it and sayin' it.
1986洛杉矶大麻缺货时
This is during the L.A. marijuana drought 1986.
我一直和那些人有联系 有点疯狂...
I still had a connection which was insane 'cause...
因为你根本弄不到货
you couldn't get any weed anywhere then.
总之 我和圣克鲁斯的一个家伙有联系
Anyway I had a connection with this hippie chick in Santa Cruz...
我的朋友都知道这事
and all my friends knew it.
他们打电话给我说 "嘿 弗雷蒂..."
They call me and say "Hey Freddy..."
我说 "嘿 伙计"
I say "Hey dude.
你弄到了吗? 能不能给我也来点?
You gettin' some? Can you get some for me too? "
他们知道我有货 所以要我替他们买点
They knew I still smoked so they asked me to buy some for them.
所以...
It got to be...
每次我买大麻时
Every time I bought some weed
都要替四五个人带点
I was buyin' for four or five people.
最后我说 去他妈的 我能靠这婊子发财了
Finally I said fuck this shit. I'm makin' this bitch rich.
她甚至不用见那些人
She didn't even have to meet these people.
所有的事都由我来办
I was doing all the work.
我就象得了痔疮一样坐不稳当 电话不停地打来
That got to be a pain in the ass people calling all the time.
甚至我租盒带子来看都会被打断六次
I couldn't even rent a tape without six fuckin' interruptions.
"你下次去弄货是什么时候? "
"When's the next time you're gettin' some? "
混蛋 让我看完这片子
"Motherfucker I'm tryin' to watch The Lost Boys.
"有货我会通知你"
When I get some I'll call you."
那些瘾君子都闻讯而来
Then these rink- a- dink potheads come by.
都是我的朋友熟人 但...
They're my friends and everything but still...
我花六十美元一袋买来 他们却不想整袋买下
I got it laid out in 60- dollar bags they don't want 60 dollars worth.
他们只要十美元的货 拆开卖可不容易
They want ten dollars' worth and breaking it up wasn't easy.
我根本不知道十美元能买多少
I don't even know what ten dollars' worth looks like.
那情形真是头疼
This was a very weird situation.
回想起86年...
Remember back in '86...
货真叫他妈紧缺
there was a major fuckin' drought.
谁都没货
Nobody had anything.
大家只好抽树叶过瘾
People were livin' on resin smokin' the wood in their pipes.
有个小妞弄到了一些货 求我替她卖掉
This chick had a bunch and she's beggin' me to sell it.
我说我不会象乔那样抽太多成
So I told her I wasn't gonna be Joe the pot man anymore...
但我得拿点卖给我的朋友
but I would take a little bit and sell it to my close friends.
她同意了 我们象谈好的那样...
She agreed and we kept the same arrangement as before...
我免费得一成...
ten percent and free pot for me...
如果我能帮她的话
if I helped her that weekend.
她要卖掉大麻
She was sellin' a brick of weed
却又不想一个人去
and didn't wanna go to the buy alone.
通常是她兄弟和她一起 但他出了麻烦
Her brother usually goes with her but he's in County unexpectedly.
- 什么麻烦? - 他的驾照在审核期
What for? His traffic tickets gone to warrant.
他们拦住他发现了这个问题 把他拘留了
They stopped him found warrants on him took him to County.
她不想一个人带着大麻到处走
She doesn't wanna walk around alone with all that weed.
我不想干 我对此有很坏的预感
I don't wanna do this.I have a very bad feeling about it.
她一直求我 求我
She keeps asking me asking me.
最后我答应了 因为实在受不了
Finally I said okay 'cause I'm sick of hearing it.
- 于是我们去车站 - 等等
- So we go to the train station... - Wait.
你把大麻带在身上去车站?
You're goin' to the train station with the weed on ya?
买家想在那交易
The guy needed it right away.
总之 我们去了车站
Anyway we get to the train station...
然后等着那家伙
and we're waitin' for the guy.
我把大麻放在一个手提袋里
I'm carryin' the weed in a carry- on bag.
我要去撒尿 所以我跟她说我要去厕所
I gotta take a piss so I tell her I'm goin' to the boy's room.
我走进厕所时猜猜谁在那?
So I walk into the men's room and who's standing there?
四个洛杉矶警察和一条德国牧羊犬
Four Los Angeles County sheriffs and a German shepherd.
- 他们在等着你? - 不 他们只是在聊天
- They're waitin' for you? - No they're just talkin'.
我走进去时 他们停了下来
When I walked in they all stopped talkin'...
然后看着我
and they looked at me.
真紧张 真他妈的紧张
That's hard. That's a fuckin' hard situation.
德国牧羊犬开始叫
German shepherd starts barking.
它向着我叫
He's barkin' at me.
我是说 它显然是在冲着我叫
I mean it's obvious he's barkin' at me.
我所有的感觉神经都僵硬了
Every nerve ending all of my senses
血在血管里尖叫
the blood in the veins was screamin
"离开这 伙计 放弃 从这离开"
"Take off man. Just bail. Get the fuck outta there."
我吓出一身冷汗 象当头淋下来一桶水
Panic hits me like a bucket of water. Bam! Right in the face.
我浑身都湿透了
I'm drenched in panic
那些警察看着我意识到有问题
and these cops are lookin' at me and they know it.
他们能闻得到 就象该死的狗能闻到一样
They can smell it sure as that fuckin' dog can.
能闻出我身上的味
They can smell it on me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
总之 我拔出枪来
So anyway I got my gun drawn.
我指着那家伙告诉他
I point it at this guy and I tell him...
"别动 他妈的别动"
"Freeze. Don't fuckin' move."
这个小白痴看着我说...
This little idiot's looking right at me and saying...
"我知道 我知道"
"I know I know."
但他的右手却偷偷伸向手套箱
But meanwhile his right hand is creepin' toward the glove box.
我对他大吼 混蛋 我会一枪崩了你
I scream at him "Asshole! I'm gonna blow you away right now!
"把手放到仪表板上"
Put your hands on the dash."
他还是看着我 点着头
He's still looking at me nodding his head.
"我知道 伙计 我知道"
"I know buddy I know."
同时他的手却仍在伸向手套箱
Meanwhile his hand is still going for the glove box.
然后我说
And I said...
"伙计 我会从你的脸上射进去...
"Buddy I'm gonna shoot you in the face...
"如果你不把手放上来的话"
if you don't put your hands up."
接着那家伙的女朋友 一个非常性感的亚洲婊子
Then this guy's girlfriend this real sexy Oriental bitch...
她开始向他尖叫 你在干什么?
she starts screaming at him: "Chuck what are you doin'?
"听警察的话 把手放到仪表板上"
Listen to the officer! Put your hands on the dash!"
然后那家伙 猛然抽出手来放到了仪表板上
So then the guy snaps out of it and puts his hands on the dash.
他拿了什么?
What was he goin' for?
他该死的驾照
His fucking registration.
- 你在开玩笑 - 不 伙计
- You're kidding. - No man!
那个白痴不知道
Stupid citizen doesn't know
他差点就把命送掉了
how close he came to gettin blown away.
只差这么一点
That close man.
你知道应付那种局面
You knew how to handle that situation.
尿湿了裤子时 跳到水里游泳就是
You shit your pants dive in and swim.
再说点卡伯特的事
Tell me more about Cabot.
我不知道
I don't know.
他是个很有趣的人
He's a cool guy.
很有趣 是个有趣的家伙
He's funny. He's a funny guy.
你记得神奇四侠吗?
You remember the Fantastic Four?
当然 有那个隐身的骚货...
Yeah with that invisible bitch...
还有霹雳火 对吗?
and "Flame on" and shit right?
没错
Thing.
是个混蛋...
Motherfucker...
看起来就象那种人
Iooks just like the Thing.
嘿 表演时间
Hey! Showtime!
拿好你的夹克 我在车上等你
Grab your jacket. I'm parked outside.
我就下来
I'll be right down.
他就下来
He'll be right down.
现在别惹我
Don't pussy out on me now.
他们不知道
They don't know.
他们什么都不知道
They don't know shit.
你不会受伤 你是他妈的传奇人物
You're not gonna get hurt. You're fuckin' Baretta.
他们相信了所有的假话 因为你非常棒
They believe every fuckin' word 'cause you're super cool.
我们的朋友来了
There goes our boy.
这家伙脑子里 得有块城砖一样大的石头
The guy has to have rocks in his head the size of Gibraltar...
才会做卧底
to work undercover.
- 你想来点吗? - 是的 给我那只熊爪
- You want one of these? - Yeah give me the bear claw.
我知道我在说什么
I know what I'm talking about.
黑种女人和白种女人不尽相同
Black women ain't the same as white women.
有些微的区别
There's a slight difference.
非常有趣 你知道我的意思
Very funny. You know what I mean.
白种女人能忍受的
What a white bitch will put up with
黑种女人一分钟也受不了
a black bitch wouldn't for a minute.
如果你越过她们的底线 她们会让你很狼狈
If you cross their line they fuck you up.
我同意粉的说法
I gotta go along with Pink on that.
那么 专家先生 如果真是这样...
Okay Mr. Expert if this is such a truism...
为什么我认识的每个黑鬼
why is it that every nigger I know
都把他们的女人象垃圾一样看待?
treats his woman like a piece of shit?
我敢说同样是那些 在外面趾高气扬的黑鬼...
I'll bet those same niggers who show their ass in public...
他们的母狗回到家时 他们就会战战兢兢
when their bitches get 'em home they chill the fuck out.
- 那些家伙不会 - 哦 会的 他们也会
- Not these guys. - Oh yeah. Those guys too.
跟你们说个故事
Tell you guys a story.
老爹的夜总会里
In one of Daddy's clubs
有个叫伊露斯的黑人女侍
there's a black cocktail waitress named Elois.
- 伊露斯? - 对 伊露斯
- Elois? - Yeah Elois.
E和Lois 我们叫她E小姐
E and Lois. We called her Lady E.
她是康普顿人吗?
Where was she from? Compton?
从拉达那来的
She's from Ladora Heights.
拉达那高地是黑人的比华利山
Ladora Heights. The black Beverly Hills.
那不是黑人的比华利山
It's not the black Beverly Hills.
那是黑人的佛得角
It's the black Palos Verdes.
总之...
Anyway...
E小姐 她是个迷死人的女人
Lady E she was a man- eater- upper. Un- fuckin'- believable.
每个曾见过她的男人 至少要向她"起立致敬"一次
Every guy who ever saw her had to jack off to her at least once.
知道她看起来象谁吗? 克里斯蒂·萝芙
You know who she looked like? Christie Love.
记得那部电视剧吗?
Remember that TV show Get Christie Love...
关于一个黑人女警的?
about the black female cop?
她总是说 "你被逮捕了 宝贝"
She always used to say "You're under arrest sugar! "
克里斯蒂·萝芙是谁演的? - 佩恩·格莉尔
- Who played Christie Love? - Pam Grier.
不是佩恩·格莉尔 她演的是另一部片子
No it wasn't Pam Grier. Pam Grier was the other one.
格莉尔是演电影的...
Pam Grier did the film.
不会演电视 萝芙只是象她而已
Christie Love was like a Pam Grier TV show without Pam Grier.
- 那是谁演的萝芙? - 我怎么知道?
- So who was Christie Love? - How should I know?
好极了 我该头疼了
Great. Now I'm totally fuckin' tortured.
不管是谁 总之很象伊露斯
Whoever it was she looked exactly like Elois.
安妮·弗朗西斯
Anne Francis.
不 那片子叫"甜蜜西部"
No. That was Honey West.
安妮·弗朗西斯是白人
Anne Francis is white.
我在试着讲故事 她看起来的确象伊露斯
I'm tryin' to tell a story here. She looked exactly like Elois.
有天晚上我们去夜总会
We come into the club one night...
那有个男侍叫卡洛斯
and there's Carlos the bartender.
墨西哥人 是我的一个朋友
He's a wetback. He's a friend of mine.
我对他说 "卡洛斯 今晚E小姐上哪了? "
I says to him "Carlos where's Lady E tonight? "
显然E小姐...
Apparently Lady E...
嫁给了一个窝囊废 一个真正的畜牲
was married to real piece of dog shit a real animal.
他对她很糟糕
He used to do things to her.
例如呢? 他都干了什么?
Like what? What would he do?
狠狠揍她?
Beat her up?
我不知道 反正他对她不好
I don't know. He just did things.
总之 有天晚上她干了件有趣的事
So anyway one night she plays it real cool.
她等到那家伙喝醉
She waits for him to get drunk.
在睡椅上睡着了之后
He falls asleep on the fuckin' couch.
她偷偷摸过去在他的老二上涂上胶水
She sneaks up on him puts some glue on his dick...
然后粘在他肚子上
and glues his dick to his belly.
我的天
Jesus Christ!
我是说真的 伙计 非常认真
I'm serious man. I'm dead serious.
他们不得不叫医生来替他慢慢割开
They had to call the paramedics to cut the prick loose.
他是不是非常恼火?
Was he all pissed off?
如果你非得他妈的倒立着撒尿
How would you feel if you had to
你会有什么感觉?
do a fuckin' handstand to take a piss?
你们喜欢说笑话然后傻笑取乐是吗?
You guys like to tell jokes and giggle and kid around huh?
笑得象一群学校里的傻妞
Giggling like a bunch of girls in the schoolyard.
让我说个笑话吧
Well let me tell a joke.
五个人坐在候审室里
Five guys sittin' in a bullpen...
在圣昆廷
San Quentin...
想知道是怎么到这来的
wonderin' how the fuck they got there.
我们做错了什么? 我们忘做了什么?
"What did we do wrong? What shouldn't we have done?
"这是你的错 他的错- - "
It's your fault his fault- - "
全是些废话
All that bullshit.
终于有个人说
Finally somebody says...
等等
"Wait a minute.
我们在计划行动时
While we were planning this caper...
"只是在无所事事地说笑话"
we just sat around tellin' fuckin' jokes."
明白了吗?
Got the message?
我不是要教训你们
I don't mean to holler at ya.
等行动结束... 我相信行动一定会成功
When this caper's over and I'm sure it'll be successful...
我们可以去夏威夷 我会和你们一起大笑
we'll go down to Hawaiian lslands I'll laugh with all of youse.
让你们看看我另外的一面
Find me a different character down there.
现在是办正事的时候
Right now it's a matter of business.
除了艾迪和我
With the exception of Eddie and myself...
你们已经知道...
who you already know...
我们在这次行动中要使用化名
we're gonna be using aliases on this job.
我们希望...
Under no circumstances...
你们任何人彼此交谈时 都不要...
do we want any one of you to relate to each other...
使用你们的真名
by your Christian names.
而且我也不希望 有任何人谈论自己的私事
And I don't want any talk about yourself personally.
包括你去过哪 你妻子的名字...
That includes where you been your wife's name...
平时你干些什么...
where you might've done time...
或是你在圣彼得堡抢过哪家银行
or a bank maybe you robbed in St. Petersburg.
如果忍不住 我希望你们只谈论...
All I want you guys to talk about if you have to...
你们想要做的事
is what you're gonna do.
将要做的事
That should do it.
这是你们的名字
These are your names...
褐先生 白先生...
Mr. Brown Mr. White...
金先生 蓝先生...
Mr. Blonde Mr. Blue...
橙先生和粉先生
Mr. Orange and Mr. Pink.
- 为什么我是粉先生? - 因为你是个同性恋 行吗?
- Why am I Mr. Pink? - Because you're a faggot! All right?
- 自己选颜色不行吗? - 不行
- Why can't we pick our own colors? - No way.
不行 试过一次 行不通
No way. Tried it once. It doesn't work.
有四个人为了做黑先生动手打架
You get four guys all fightin' over who gets to be Mr. Black.
他们互不相识 所以没人想退让
They don't know each other so nobody wants to back down.
不行 我来定 你是粉先生
No way. I pick. You're Mr. Pink.
该庆幸你不是黄先生
Be thankful you're not Mr. Yellow.
但是褐先生 和屎先生很接近
But Mr. Brown that's too close to Mr. Shit.
粉先生听来象"女阴"先生
Mr. Pink sounds like Mr. Pussy.
紫先生怎么样?
How about Mr. Purple?
听起来不错 我要做紫先生
That's sounds good. I'll be Mr. Purple.
你不是紫先生
You're not Mr. Purple.
另一个买卖有人叫紫先生了 你就叫粉先生
Some guy on some other job is Mr. Purple. You're Mr. Pink!
谁会在乎你叫什么?
Who cares what your name is?
你说得容易 你是白先生
Easy for you to say. You're Mr. White.
你有个听来很酷的名字
You have a cool- sounding name.
如果你不介意叫粉先生 你愿意交换吗?
If it's no big deal to be Mr. Pink you wanna trade?
不准私自交换
Nobody's tradin' with anybody.
这不是他妈的市政讨论会 你知道的
This ain't a goddamn fuckin' city council meeting you know.
听着 粉先生
Now listen up Mr. Pink.
这件事上你有两条路可走
There's two ways you can go on this job...
我的路或者那条公路
my way or the highway.
你选哪条? 粉先生
What's it gonna be Mr. Pink?
老天 他妈的忘了这些好了
Jesus Christ Joe. Fuckin' forget about it.
这名字很衬我 我是粉先生 继续吧
It's beneath me. I'm Mr. Pink. Let's move on.
我觉得高兴时自然会继续
I'll move on when I feel like it.
你们都明白了吗?
Do all you guys got the goddamn message?
我扯着嗓子向你们喊叫 几乎都说不出话来了
I'm so goddamn mad hollerin' at you guys I can hardly talk.
我们开始行动吧
Let's go to work.
我们重复一次 你在哪?
Let's go over it. Where are you?
我站在外边守住门 不让任何人进出
I stand outside and guard the door.I don't let anybody go in or out.
- 褐先生 - 他等在车里
- Mr. Brown. - He waits in the car.
我给他信号 他就把车开到门口
I give him the signal he pulls up in front.
金先生和蓝先生
Mr. Blonde and Mr. Blue.
控制人群 他们控制顾客和店员
Crowd control. They handle the customers and the employees.
- 那个妞的屁股 - 正好坐在我的老二上
- That girl's ass. - Sittin' right here on my dick.
我和粉先生呢?
Myself and Mr. Pink?
你们俩抓住经理让他给你们钻石
You two take the manager and make him give you the diamonds.
我们的目标是钻石
We're there for those stones period.
因为没有监视器添乱
Since no display cases are being
不会有警报声
fucked with no alarms should go off.
我们要在两分钟内出来 不能拖延一秒
We're out in two minutes not one second longer.
如果经理不给你钻石怎么办?
What if the manager won't give you the diamonds?
象这样的店铺都有保险
A store like this is insured up the ass.
无论你要什么他们都不会反抗
They're not supposed to give you any resistance whatsoever.
如果有顾客或店员
If you get a customer or an employee
自以为是查尔斯·布朗森...
who thinks he's Charles Bronson...
把枪塞进他的鼻孔
smash their nose with your gun.
把他放倒在地上 任何人都会害怕
Drops him right to the floor. Everyone jumps.
他会跪在地上尖叫 鼻孔里鲜血直冒
He falls down screaming blood squirts out of his nose.
搞定一个之后就没人敢再说废话
Freaks everybody out. Nobody says fuckin' shit after that.
也许有哪个母狗会跟你废话
Some bitch might talk shit to you.
看她一眼 似乎接下来就轮到她 她就会闭上臭嘴
Give her a look like she's next. Watch her shut the fuck up.
如果是经理 那就不同
If it's the manager that's different.
经理懂得不要乱来
The managers know not to fuck around...
如果他不合作
so if he's giving you static...
自以为是个真正的牛仔
he probably thinks he's a real cowboy
那只好让这杂种吃点苦头
so you gotta that bastard in two.
他不开口就切掉他一根手指
If he won't tell ya something cut off one of his fingers.
小指 然后告诉他下一根是拇指
The little one. Then tell him his thumb's next.
之后他会告诉你 他是否穿了女式内衣
After that he'll tell you if he wears ladies underwear.
我饿了 去买个玉米卷
I'm hungry. Let's get a taco.
妈的
Fuck.
老天
Jesus.
我瞎了 伙计 我瞎了
I'm blind man. I'm fuckin' blind.
不 只不过是血流进了你的眼睛
No you just got blood in your eyes.
他死了?
Is he dead?
他是不是死了?
Did he die or not?
我们走
Let's go.
停下 出来
Hold it! Get out!
从他妈的车里出来
Get out of the fuckin' car!
对不起 对不起 拉里
I'm sorry. I'm sorry Larry.
真不敢相信她想杀了我 谁他妈会料到呢?
I can't believe she killed me. Who'd have fucking thought that?
嘿 现在别说废话了
Hey just cancel that shit right now.
你受了伤 伤得确实很重
You're hurt. You're hurt real fuckin' bad.
但你不会死
But you ain't dying.
我流出的这些血让我害怕 拉里
All this blood's scaring the shit out of me Larry.
我快死了 我知道
I'm gonna die. I know it.
他妈的怎么了?
What the fuck happened?
他猛砍这警察的脸 割掉他的耳朵
He slashed the cop's face cut off his ear
还想活活烧他
and was gonna burn him alive.
什么? 我没听到
What? I didn't hear you.
我是说...
I said...
金发疯了
Blonde went crazy.
他猛砍这警察的脸 割掉他的耳朵
He slashed the cop's face cut off his ear
还想烧死他
and was gonna burn him alive.
这个警察?
This cop?
他发疯了? 就象这样子?
He went crazy? Something like that?
更坏还是更好?
Worse or better?
艾迪 他想点火 伙计
Eddie he was pulling a burn man.
他想杀了那警察和我
He was gonna kill the cop and me.
你们进来的时候
When you guys walked in
他想杀了你们带着钻石逃跑
he was gonna kill you and run with the diamonds.
我跟你说过什么?
What'd I tell ya?
那个变态的杂种是个冷血疯子
That sick piece of shit was a stone- cold psycho.
你该问问那警察 而不是杀了他
You should've asked the cop not just killed him.
他用刀割他的时候说了
He talked about what he was gonna do when
他想干什么
he was slicing him up.
我不相信
I don't buy it.
这没道理
Doesn't make sense.
我他妈的全都相信
Makes perfect fuckin' sense to me.
你没看到行动的时候他是怎么干的 我们看到过
You didn't see how he acted during the job. We did.
他没说错 耳朵是割下来的
He's right. The ear's hacked off.
让我再大声说一遍 因为我想弄清楚
Let me just say this out loud 'cause I wanna get this straight.
你说金先生...
You're saying that Mr. Blonde...
想杀了你...
was gonna kill you...
然后在我们回来时干掉我们...
and then when we got back he was gonna kill us...
带着钻石逃走
take the diamonds and scram.
我说得对不对? 这是你的故事?
I'm right about that right? That's your story?
我以我母亲的灵魂发誓...
I swear on my mother's soul...
就是这样
that's what happened.
你杀死的这个人刚从监狱放出来
The man you killed just got released from prison.
他在一个 满是违禁品的公司仓库里被抓
He got caught at a company warehouse full of hot items.
他可以他妈的脱罪
He could've fuckin' walked.
只要他说出我老爹的名字
All he had to do was say my dad's name
但他没有 他守口如瓶
but he didn't; he kept his mouth shut.
他象个男人那样什么都没说
He did his fuckin' time like a man.
他为我们坐了四年牢
He did four years for us.
所以 橙先生...
So Mr. Orange...
你说我的这个好朋友...
you're telling me that this good friend of mine...
替我父亲坐了四年牢的人...
who did four years for my father...
四年里从没妥协
who in four years never made a deal
没向他们说出半个字的人
no matter what they offered him...
你告诉我现在他自由了...
you're telling me that now that he's free...
并且我们向他作出了很好的承诺...
and we're making good on our commitment to him...
他却决定 不算这个该死的警察...
he's just gonna decide out of the fucking blue...
把我们全干掉?
to rip us off?
为什么你不告诉我真相?
Why don't you tell me what really happened.
到底怎么回事?
What the hell for?
用不着再废话
It'd just be more bullshit.
这个人出卖了我们
This man set us up.
爸 我很抱歉 但我不知道发生了什么事
Dad I'm sorry but I don't know what's happening.
- 没关系 我知道 - 你在说什么?
- It's all right. I do. - What are you talking about?
这个愚蠢的废物是洛杉矶警方的人
That lump of shit's workin' with the L.A.P.D.
我他妈的一点都不明白...
I don't have the slightest fucking idea...
你在说什么
what you're talking about.
乔 我不知道你以为自己知道什么 但你错了
Joe I don't know what you think you know but you're wrong.
的确如此
Like hell I am.
你要相信我 你弄错了
Trust me on this. You've made a mistake.
他是个好伙计
He's a good kid.
我明白你非常恼火
I understand you're super- fuckin'- pissed.
我们都很激动
We're all real emotional.
但是你弄错了对象
But you're barking up the wrong tree.
我了解他 他没有那样做
I know this man. He wouldn't do that.
你不知道警察的把戏
You don't know jack shit!
我知道
I do.
这个杂种向警方告密...
The cocksucker tipped off the cops...
害死了褐先生和蓝先生
and got Mr. Brown and Mr. Blue killed.
- 蓝先生死了? - 是的
- Mr. Blue is dead? - Dead as Dillinger.
你怎么知道这些?
How do you know all this?
他是我唯一不能完全信任的人
He was the only one I wasn't 100 percent on.
我该检讨自己
I should have my head examined going ahead
在没有十足把握时就开始行动
when I wasn't 100 percent.
- 那就是你的证据? - 有直觉你就用不着证据
- That's your proof? - With instinct you don't need proof.
我以前忽视了 但再也不会
I ignored it before but no more.
你是不是他妈的疯了?
Have you lost your fuckin' mind?
我不会让你犯一个大错误
I'm not gonna let you make a terrible mistake.
拜托 伙计们 没人想这样
Come on guys. Nobody wants this.
我们该他妈的表现得专业点
We're supposed to be fuckin' professionals.
拉里 听着...
Larry look...
我们合作过很久
it's been quite a long time.
很多生意
A lot of jobs.
不需要这样 伙计
There's no need for this man.
我们都把枪放下
Let's just put our guns down...
把事情弄清楚
and let's settle this...
他妈的好好谈谈
with a fucking conversation.
乔 如果你杀了他 你会是下一个
Joe if you kill that man you die next.
再说一次 你杀他 我就杀你
Repeat: you kill him you die next.
拉里 我们是朋友
Larry we have been friends.
你尊敬我父亲我也尊敬你
You respect my dad and I respect you...
但是我会向你开枪
but I'll put bullets in you.
现在你把那该死的枪放下
You put that fuckin' gun down now.
该死的 乔...
Goddamn you Joe...
别让我这么做
don't make me do this.
拉里 别拿枪指着我老爹
Larry you stop pointin' that gun at my dad!
对不起 伙计
I'm sorry kid.
看来我们还要...
Looks like we're gonna...
再支持一会
do a little time.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
拉里...
Larry...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我...
I'm...
很抱歉
so sorry.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我...
I'm...
对不起...
sorry...
弗雷泽
Freeze!
放下枪 伙计
Drop the fucking gun buddy!
- 马上 - 把枪放下
- Now! - Put the gun down!
- 别那么做 - 放下枪 伙计
- Don't do it! - Drop the gun man!
- 把他妈的枪放下 - 我们会打爆你的头
- Drop the fucking gun! - We're gonna blow you away!